<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
      <game id="237" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./1080 Snowboarding (JU) (M2) [!].v64</path>
          <name>1080 TenEighty Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja)</name>
          <desc>You’re taking a Tahoe 155 snowboard down a steep, bumpy incline at night and you’re about to top off an Indy Nosebone with a 360° Air, and you haven’t even left your living room!  You’re Playing 1080° (Ten Eighty) Snowboarding, a game so intense you’ll be brushing the snow off your goggles.  With five different boarders, eight different Lamar snowboards, more than 25 tricks, a Half-Pipe and six different courses, this is as close as you’ll get to the real thing without hopping on the next ski lift.&#xA;&#xA;* Six game modes and courses!&#xA;* 2-Player simultaneous play!&#xA;* Over 25 different tricks!&#xA;* Compatible with Rumble Pak accessory.</desc>
          <image>./images/1080 Snowboarding (JU) (M2) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.67143</rating>
          <releasedate>19980401T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1052" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./AeroFighters Assault (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>AeroFighters Assault (USA)</name>
          <desc>The Aero Fighters Assault team needs your help to save the Earth from the evil Phutta Morgana organization and their machines of doom. Join the battle and choose your fighter from 6 different aircrafts with unique missiles and special weapons to wipe out your enemies in 3D-environment!</desc>
          <image>./images/AeroFighters Assault (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Paradigm Entertainment</developer>
          <publisher>Video System</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="238" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./007 - The World is Not Enough (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>007 - The World Is Not Enough (USA)</name>
          <desc>007:The World Is Not Enough was released in 2000 as a video game adaption of the same-titled movie and successor to GoldenEye 007. The storyline generally follows the movie plot, whereas James Bond has to protect Elektra King from a terrorist called Renard; but as it surprisingly turns out that King is working together with Renard to blow up Istanbul with a nuclear submarine in order to take over the World&#39;s oil market, Bond teams up with Dr. Christmas Jones to stop their plans. The N64 version features 14 Levels in the Single-Player campaign as well as Multiplayer Modes with 4-Player Support &amp; additional AI bots.</desc>
          <image>./images/007 - The World is Not Enough (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.67</rating>
          <releasedate>20001017T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Eurocom</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1059" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./All-Star Baseball 2001 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>All-Star Baseball 2001 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The last All-Star Baseball release on the N64 once again includes some new features as well as improvements in relation to previous play modes &amp; options. For 2001, a new team is included, The Coopertown Legends, featuring a selection of some of the finest players to ever grace the MLB, including Yogi Berra, Willie Stargell and Reggie Jackson.&#xA;Along with the legends team, you can choose from every player, team and stadium from the real 2000 MLB season. Each player includes facial expressions and looks inspired to realism, plus motion-captured player movements, batting stances and reactions to key events during play.</desc>
          <image>./images/All-Star Baseball 2001 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Acclaim</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="16736" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Bangai-O (J) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Bakuretsu Muteki Bangaioh (Japan)</name>
          <desc>In Bakuretsu Muteki Bangaioh, a multi-directional shooter video game developed by Treasure, two young mech-pilots, Riki and his sister Mami share command of the powerful humanoid-shaped Bangai-O and battle villains from the &#34;Cosmo Gang&#34;, guilty of fruit contraband, and lots of gun turrets, bombs and robots through 44 levels.</desc>
          <image>./images/Bangai-O (J) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19990903T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Treasure</developer>
          <publisher>Conspiracy Entertainment</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="162" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Banjo-Kazooie (U) (V1.0) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</name>
          <desc>In Banjo-Kazooie a bear named Banjo and a bird named Kazooie live on Spiral Mountain. One day Gruntilda the witch kidnaps Banjo&#39;s sister Tooty, to steal her beauty via a transformation device. Banjo and Kazooie set out on a dangerous adventure to rescue Tooty.</desc>
          <image>./images/Banjo-Kazooie (U) (V1.0) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75556</rating>
          <releasedate>19980630T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rareware</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="244" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Body Harvest (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Body Harvest (USA)</name>
          <desc>The year is 2016. Humanity has been reduced to a few survivors inhabiting the orbital space station Omega. Over the course of the history, aliens visited the Earth every twenty-five years, &#34;harvesting&#34; humans as an organic material. Eventually, they launch an assault on the last remnants of the human race. But Adam Drake, a genetically engineered soldier, comes into possession of a time-traveling device. He uses it to travel to the time periods of human history when aliens performed their deadly attacks. The fate of humanity is in his hands.&#xA;&#xA;Body Harvest is an action and driving game with a mission-based structure. The protagonist travels to various locations and eras (e.g. Greece during World War II, Siberia in the 1990s, etc.) with the goal of stopping alien invasions. Missions can be accessed by traveling to specified areas on the map. Adam can move on foot and use his weapons to kill aliens; however, vehicles usually prove to be a more reliable way of tackling most missions. Adam can use most of his weapons while in a vehicle; in addition, some vehicles are outfitted with their own weapons.</desc>
          <image>./images/Body Harvest (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5333300000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>19981020T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>DMA Design</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1070" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Blast Corps (U) (V1.1) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Blast Corps (USA) (Rev A)</name>
          <desc>Blast Corps is a 1997 video game for the Nintendo 64 developed by Rare and published by Nintendo. Destroy a series of buildings or objects using a variety of unique demolition vehicles, in order to mainly clear a path for trucks carrying defective nuclear missiles.</desc>
          <image>./images/Blast Corps (U) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rare</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="176" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Banjo-Tooie (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Banjo-Tooie (USA)</name>
          <desc>Two years after Banjo &amp; Kazooie rescued Banjo&#39;s sister Tooty, the antagonist Gruntilda Winkybunion and her sisters, Mingella and Blobbelda, are planning to restore Gruntilda&#39;s body to its original form. Banjo and Kazooie must stop them before it is too late.</desc>
          <image>./images/Banjo-Tooie (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76</rating>
          <releasedate>20001119T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rareware</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1067" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Beetle Adventure Racing! (U) (M3) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Beetle Adventure Racing! (USA) (En,Fr,De)</name>
          <desc>Take control of a collection of the latest Volkswagen Beetle &#34;2.0&#34; models, from street type to off-road designs, and race across varying road types that will test your speed and endurance!&#xA;Find shortcuts or use nitro boosts to finish first in order to move on to the next track. If the computer AI is to easy for you, battle against a friend in two player race mode or challenge up to 4 people in a special Battle Mode, with added abilities including weapons, from mines and rockets to magical elements, while collecting the flag and finding the exit!</desc>
          <image>./images/Beetle Adventure Racing! (U) (M3) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.675</rating>
          <releasedate>19990319T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Paradigm Entertainment</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="246" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</name>
          <desc>Before Reinhardt Schneider and Carrie Fernandez confronted Dracula, a magical warrior embarked on a quest that would ultimately lead him to Dracula&#39;s lair. Take control of Cornell, a powerful werewolf, who is seeking out the evil minions responsible for his sister&#39;s disappearance. Armed with the power to morph from human to werewolf, Cornell is destined to rescure his sister from a sinister plan and rid the world of Dracula once and for all. Will he succeed or fail? Will the past unravel the future? Discover the legacy in this exciting prequel.</desc>
          <image>./images/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.65</rating>
          <releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="5648" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Custom Robo V2 (J) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Custom Robo V2 (Japan)</name>
          <desc>Second and last Custom Robo title developed for the Nintendo 64. It is also the first title of the series to allow up to four players to play, instead of up to two players.  Custom Robo takes place in Nintendo&#39;s own collect-and-battle style RPG genre simi</desc>
          <image>./images/Custom Robo V2 (J) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>20001110T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Noise Factory</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo - Noise</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="16995" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Custom Robo (J) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Custom Robo (Japan)</name>
          <desc>Custom Robo is sort of a sci-fi action take on Nintendo&#39;s own collect-and-battle style Pokemon titles. In the game&#39;s story mode, you slip into the role of a young boy who has just built his very own toy robot who goes by the name of Lei. Together with your cousin, you head down towards Robo Station to take part in a giant Custom Robo battle championship that takes place in the local Holosseum. The ultimate goal is to improve your skills so that you can defeat the champion Custom Robo builder of them all, Mamoru. Gameplay involves robo customization and frantic action battles in confined 3D arenas. Followed by a sequel.</desc>
          <image>./images/Custom Robo (J) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19991208T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Noise</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="178" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Diddy Kong Racing (U) (M2) (V1.1) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Diddy Kong Racing (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev A)</name>
          <desc>Timber the Tiger&#39;s parents go on vacation and leave their son in charge of the island they live on, leaving him and his friends to race for fun. Their enjoyment is derailed when an evil, intergalactic, pig wizard named Wizpig arrives at peaceful Timber&#39;s Island and attempts to take over after he conquered his own planet&#39;s racetracks. He turns the four island&#39;s guardians: Tricky the Triceratops, Bubbler the Octopus, Bluey the Walrus and Smokey the Dragon into his henchmen. The only solution available to the island&#39;s inhabitants is to defeat Wizpig in an elaborate series of races that involves cars, hovercrafts, and airplanes. Drumstick, the best racer on the island, failed this challenge and was transformed into a frog by Wizpig&#39;s black magic. Timber recruits a team of 7 racers: Diddy Kong, the first recruit; Conker (Dixie Kong on DS), recruited by Diddy; Banjo (Tiny Kong on DS), also recruited by Diddy; Krunch, Diddy&#39;s enemy who follows after him; Tiptup, an inhabitant of Timber&#39;s island; Pipsy, another inhabitant of Timber&#39;s island; and Bumper, another inhabitant of Timber&#39;s island. They eventually complete all of Wizpig&#39;s challenges and confront Wizpig himself to a race and defeat him. Shortly afterwards, Wizpig leaves for his home planet, Future Fun Land. Fearing that Wizpig would again attempt to invade Timber&#39;s Island, the islanders travel to Future Fun Land for a second challenge. When Wizpig loses the second race, the rocket he rides on malfunctions and blasts him to a distant planet and peace returns to Timber Island for good.</desc>
          <image>./images/Diddy Kong Racing (U) (M2) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7466700000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>19971121T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rareware</developer>
          <publisher>Rareware</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="249" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Conker&#39;s Bad Fur Day (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Conker&#39;s Bad Fur Day (USA)</name>
          <desc>The day after his 21st birthday bash, Conker&#39;s sporting the worst hangover ever, and he just can&#39;t seem to find his way home. Prepare to stagger through randy, raunchy, raucous scenarios crammed full of bad manners, twisted humor, and graphic bodily functions. Unless you&#39;re a fan of violence, foul language, and racy innuendo, you&#39;d best steer clear of this one.</desc>
          <image>./images/Conker&#39;s Bad Fur Day (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76429</rating>
          <releasedate>20010304T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
          <publisher>Rare Ltd.</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1089" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Disney&#39;s Donald Duck - Goin&#39; Quackers (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Donald Duck - Goin&#39; Quackers (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</name>
          <desc>Keeping Donald content is about as easy as herding cats, but everyone&#39;s favorite fusspot really goes off the deep end when malodorous magician Merlock duck-naps Daisy. To add insult to injury, Donald&#39;s uppity cousin, Gladstone Gander, vows to rescue Daisy. Thus begins Donald&#39;s great race to reach Daisy first and foil Merlock&#39;s nefarious plans.</desc>
          <image>./images/Disney&#39;s Donald Duck - Goin&#39; Quackers (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20001019T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
          <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="265" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Duck Dodgers Starring Daffy Duck (U) (M3) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Duck Dodgers Starring Daffy Duck (USA) (En,Fr,Es)</name>
          <desc>Marvin The Martian has developed an ultimate weapon that will allow him to finally destroy Earth, which will ultimately allow him to take control of the universe. Upon the demonstration of the weapon, a slight snag hinders Marvin from completing his devious deed. The Weapon is out of Atoms, which it runs on, so he sends his minions (All of which are characters from the Looney Tune universe) to gather Atoms to fuel his weapon.&#xA;&#xA;Duck Dodgers is informed by his academy of Marvin&#39;s deeds and sets out to find the one-hundred Atoms before Marvin can. This ultimately has Dodgers and his sidekick, Cadet, trekking to four different planets, including a large pirate ship, to obtain the upper-hand over Marvin.</desc>
          <image>./images/Duck Dodgers Starring Daffy Duck (U) (M3) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20001216T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Paradigm</developer>
          <publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="250" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Donkey Kong 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>K. Rool has kidnapped the Kongs! Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky&#39;s Pineapple Launcher or Lanky&#39;s Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny&#39;s Ponytail Twirl. Even rocket to the sky with Diddy&#39;s Jetbarrel!</desc>
          <image>./images/Donkey Kong 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8</rating>
          <releasedate>19991124T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rare</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1097" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Excitebike 64 (U) (V1.0) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Excitebike 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Experience extreme MX! You grind your way through the hairpin turn, a wall of mud exploding in your wake. Your next jump launches you into the air - you pull off a spectacular double no-footed can-can and become an instant legend! In Excitebike 64, you&#39;ll find all the high-flying action, heart-stopping stunts and bone-jarring crashes of the extreme sport of motocross. It&#39;ll set the daredevil inside you free. 20 stadium tracks and awesome outdoor courses - plus six different riders with six unique styles!</desc>
          <image>./images/Excitebike 64 (U) (V1.0) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.675</rating>
          <releasedate>20000430T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Ninteno</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1100" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./F-1 World Grand Prix (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>F-1 World Grand Prix (USA)</name>
          <desc>The game consists of five gameplay modes: Grand Prix, a course-by-course simulation of the 1997 season; Exhibition, a single race; Time Trial, a race against the clock and Challenge, which comprised real scenarios from the 1997 season-examples include trying to win the 1997 Hungarian Grand Prix as Damon Hill or beating Jean Alesi as David Coulthard in the 1997 Italian Grand Prix. The final mode allowed 2 players to compete in a single, split-screen race.</desc>
          <image>./images/F-1 World Grand Prix (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19980914T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Paradigm Entertainment,</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1101" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./F-1 World Grand Prix II (E) (M4) [!].v64</path>
          <name>F-1 World Grand Prix II (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</name>
          <desc>F1 WGP 2 pretty much sports the same features as the first game. The game has 4 modes of play: the championship season mode, the exhibition race, time trials, and the challenge mode. R and Z are used to shift gears, the analog stick is used to steer the car, A is the accelerator and B is the brake. The C-buttons allow for camera changes and backmirror views. It&#39;s pretty much the same setup and how these work are pretty much unchanged from the first game to the second.</desc>
          <image>./images/F-1 World Grand Prix II (E) (M4) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6333300000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Paradigm Entertainment</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="958" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Extreme-G XG2 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Extreme-G XG2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>This iteration, as with all Extreme-G games, is about futuristic racing: pilots race plasma-powered Tron-like bikes in an intergalactic Grand Prix at speeds that are over 999 mph.  It is possible to break the sound barrier in this game, creating a sonic boom. While travelling at supersonic speeds, all game sounds are muted except the sound of the vehicle travelling.  If the bike slows down to below supersonic speeds, another sonic boom can be heard and all game sounds will resume.  The emphasis is on speed and creative racetrack design, with tracks looping through all three dimensions like roller coasters.</desc>
          <image>./images/Extreme-G XG2 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19981007T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
          <genre>Vehicle Simulation</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="957" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Extreme-G (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Extreme-G (USA)</name>
          <desc>Extreme-G is set in the distant future where Earth is a mere wasteland.  From their new found planet the human colonists watch with joy as their remote controlled power-bikes wreak havoc through their ancient cities.  There is only one winner, the first to cross the line… or the last to survive.</desc>
          <image>./images/Extreme-G (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19971025T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="10836" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./F-ZERO X (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>F-Zero X (USA)</name>
          <desc>It&#39;s you against 29 other machines competing for the title of F-Zero X Champion. You&#39;re racing at speeds of over 1,000 km/h high above the atmosphere. Your competition comes from every corner of the galaxy and won&#39;t shed a tear at the thought of smashing you off the track. With four-player simultaneous gameplay and the Rumble Pak accessory, you have the fastest racing game on the N64 system!</desc>
          <image>./images/F-ZERO X (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.71429</rating>
          <releasedate>19980714T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1102" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./FIFA - Road to World Cup 98 (U) (M7) [!].v64</path>
          <name>FIFA - Road to World Cup 98 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Sv)</name>
          <desc>The game includes an official soundtrack and had a refined graphics engine, team and player customisation options, 16 stadiums, improved artificial intelligence and the popular &#34;Road to World Cup&#34; mode, with all 173 FIFA-registered national teams. No subsequent edition of the FIFA series has attempted to replicate FIFA 98&#39;s inclusion of every FIFA national team. With the new graphical improvements, players were able to have individual faces. However, they looked more like expressions.</desc>
          <image>./images/FIFA - Road to World Cup 98 (U) (M7) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19971220T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>EA Sports</developer>
          <publisher>EA</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="959" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Flying Dragon (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Flying Dragon (USA)</name>
          <desc>Two games in one: Flying Dragon is the ONE and ONLY game that will entertain the entire family. Create your ideal fighting game using the most customizable interface yet offered. Choose between RPG-style and &#34;virtual&#34; tournament combat. Flying Dragon is never the same game twice! Over 20 different characters and 200 different items. Save your characters on a Controller Pak and play them against your friends!</desc>
          <image>./images/Flying Dragon (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19980731T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Culture Brain</developer>
          <publisher>Natsume</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="252" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Fighter&#39;s Destiny 2 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Fighter Destiny 2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Enter the arena and do battle with the toughest, most skilled martial arts experts on the planet. As one of the international fighting elite, you&#39;ll vie to become the true authority of hand-to-hand combat. Your destiny awaits. Defeat any of your 11 opponents and gain their abilities. Launch 5 different modes of attack, from Training to Record Attack. Adjust scoring, ring sizes and difficulty settings. Compete in points-based martial arts tournaments. Force your opponent to relive defeat in instant replay. Gain new abilities and skills when you face the Master in the Fighter&#39;s Arena.</desc>
          <image>./images/Fighter&#39;s Destiny 2 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20000622T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Imagineer</developer>
          <publisher>Southpeak</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1105" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Fighter&#39;s Destiny (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Fighters Destiny (USA)</name>
          <desc>Defeat the Masters of the Fight in a head-on bout of power and skill. Fighters Destiny demands everything you have, everything you are and throws it right back at you in truly amazing, unstoppable 3D action. Prepare to fight every step of the way as you master the moves and unlock the secrets to fulfill your ultimate destiny!</desc>
          <image>./images/Fighter&#39;s Destiny (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19980127T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Imagineer/Genki</developer>
          <publisher>Ocean</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="254" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Forsaken 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Forsaken 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Forsaken is a first-person shoot &#39;em up in which you have complete movement freedom in 3 dimensions, as you accelerate, swerve and strafe your craft, making for gameplay resembling Descent. Each level has a defined exit which must be reached within a tight time limit. The surrounding areas are collapsing around you, with spikes and turbine fans among your hazards. Be very aware of other craft out to take all you have, as they alter their approach based on your weaponry (from the 25 featured in the game) and past encounters.</desc>
          <image>./images/Forsaken 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.66667</rating>
          <releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Iguana</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1112" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Golden Nugget 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Golden Nugget 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The famed Golden Nugget Las Vegas hotel and casino is the setting for the following games: Blackjack: The goal of blackjack is to get the total point value of your cards to 21 without going over; Craps: The objective of craps is to bet on the outcome of dice rolls; Five-card draw: Like most poker games, the point of five card draw is to have the best hand after the final betting round; Roulette: The goal of roulette is to correctly guess which slot the ball will stop on; Seven-card stud: The goal is have the best hand over other opponents; Video poker: The goal of video poker is to make the best possible hand. Unlike other poker games, there are no opponents. You win a certain multiplier of your bet based on your hand; Texas Hold &#39;Em: To objective is to have a better hand than your opponents. Big Six: Similar to roulette, this game has players try to successfully predict what symbol the wheel will stop on; Mini-Baccarat: The goal of mini-baccarat is to guess which hand is closer to 9 without going over; Slot machines: In order to win in slots, players must match a winning combination of symbols. These symbols vary from slot machine to slot machine. There are six different slot machines in this game.</desc>
          <image>./images/Golden Nugget 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19981208T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Puzzle</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="160" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./GoldenEye 007 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>007 - GoldenEye (USA)</name>
          <desc>You are Bond, James Bond.&#xA;&#xA;You are assigned to covert operations connected with the GoldenEye weapons satellite.  M will brief you on your mission and objectives from London.  Q Branch will support your efforts with a plentiful supply of weapons and gadgets.  Moneypenny offers you light-hearted best wishes and you’re off!&#xA;&#xA;Your mission begins in the heavily guarded chemical warfare facility at the Byelomorye Dam in the USSR.  Look and shoot in any direction as you navigate 12 interactive 3-D environments.  Use stealth and force as you see fit in matters of international security.  Consider the military personnel expendable.  You are licensed to kill!&#xA;&#xA;* Exciting 3-D environments.&#xA;* Highly intelligent enemies!&#xA;* Numerous Q gadgets and weapons!&#xA;* Battery-backed memory saves game progress!</desc>
          <image>./images/GoldenEye 007 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76</rating>
          <releasedate>19970823T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rareware</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1114" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Harvest Moon 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Harvest Moon 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Retire to the country for a new challenge in Harvest Moon 64. Hard work is rewarded as you struggle to bring prosperity back to a neglected farm. Work the land, pick up odd-jobs, and get to know the neighbors. Harvest Moon 64 has all the charm of the original Super Nintendo classic, plus many new surprises.&#xA;&#xA;* Tons of new seasonal vegetables and fruits.&#xA;* Raise cows, chickens, and sheep.&#xA;* New items and gifts. Including tools that increase in power as you master them.&#xA;* One of town&#39;s five eligible women may prove to be the love of your life.&#xA;* Celebrate seasonal festivals with the nearby townsfolk.&#xA;* Enjoy local horse and dog racing.</desc>
          <image>./images/Harvest Moon 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.625</rating>
          <releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Toy Box Studios</developer>
          <publisher>Natsume</publisher>
          <genre>Construction and Management Simulation</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1117" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Hybrid Heaven (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Hybrid Heaven (USA)</name>
          <desc>A gunshot echoes through the tunnels of the New York subway system. A secret service agent lies dying, and Diaz, with a gun gripped tightly in his hand, flees and stumbles into a strange underground world where a secret society of genetically engineered hybrid clones threaten to subvert the population of the outside world. Experience New York City&#39;s secret night life in Hybrid Heaven, a unique, fully-immersive action RPG that combines fighting, action, and role playing into a story of alien invasion, scientific experimentation, and murder. Unravel the secrets of the hybrid society, the future of humanity, and the true identity of Diaz.</desc>
          <image>./images/Hybrid Heaven (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.45</rating>
          <releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="258" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Hydro Thunder (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Hydro Thunder (USA)</name>
          <desc>The gameplay of Hydro Thunder consists of racing high-tech speedboats through treacherous environments, from the cold seas of the Arctic Circle, to a post-apocalyptic, flooded version of New York City.</desc>
          <image>./images/Hydro Thunder (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Midway Games</developer>
          <publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
          <genre>Vehicle Simulation</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="260" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Jet Force Gemini (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Jet Force Gemini (USA)</name>
          <desc>The insect invasion has begun.&#xA;&#xA;The galaxy is being infested by the evil Mizar and his horde of Drones. Already, the planet of Goldwood has been subjugated and the peaceful Trabals enslaved. With an arsenal of mega-weapons at their disposal, the Jet Force Gemini team must travel in search of Mizar&#39;s lair - rescuing Tribals and splattering Drones along the way. But can Juno, Vela and their faithful dog, Lupus, exterminate the deadly threat before it&#39;s too late?</desc>
          <image>./images/Jet Force Gemini (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.72</rating>
          <releasedate>19991011T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rare</developer>
          <publisher>Rare</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1123" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./International Superstar Soccer 2000 (U) (M2) [!].v64</path>
          <name>International Superstar Soccer 2000 (USA) (En,Es)</name>
          <desc>The undisputed king of football returns... Experience the new Career Mode - bring youngsters through the ranks to create individual star players. Smoother animations and gameplay. ISS 2000 is the choice of champions - nothing gets as close to the beautiful game.</desc>
          <image>./images/International Superstar Soccer 2000 (U) (M2) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.725</rating>
          <releasedate>20000803T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="261" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Killer Instinct Gold (U) (V1.0) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Killer Instinct Gold (USA)</name>
          <desc>Killer Instinct Gold rocks the gaming world with its earth-shattering moves and unbelievable graphics. Your battles unfold with lightning-fast action and fluid character animation at 60 frames per second. We faithfully duplicated all the features that made Killer Instinct 2 an arcade hit. We&#39;ve even thrown in a complete training mode to school you on all the moves! The eye-popping graphics, the explosive hits and jaw-dropping combos make Killer Instinct Gold the only fighting game you&#39;ll ever want in your house!</desc>
          <image>./images/Killer Instinct Gold (U) (V1.0) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19961125T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1128" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Knife Edge - Nose Gunner (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Knife Edge - Nose Gunner (USA)</name>
          <desc>Kemco offers up a title that introduces brand new gameplay concepts to the Nintendo 64 with KNIFE EDGE: Nose Gunner. The storyline takes the player to Mars and beyond, battling against enemies of an alien variety. The gameplay takes classic shooting action and sticks it in a first-person perspective, resulting in an intense and action-packed affair. However, the levels are not free roaming, as the action travels along predetermined rails that offer multiple paths to be determined by the player. In addition to the one-player Story mode, there is a Practice mode that allows the player to sharpen their shooting skills. To appease fans of multiplayer, there is the option to play with up to four people in the Story mode, as well as fight against each other in the Team Battle mode. KNIFE EDGE: Nose Gunner for the Nintendo 64 offers a large amount of options and modes, as well as an exciting shooting adventure that is truly unique among N64 titles.</desc>
          <image>./images/Knife Edge - Nose Gunner (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.55</rating>
          <releasedate>19981110T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Kemco</developer>
          <publisher>Kemco</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="264" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Knockout Kings 2000 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Knockout Kings 2000 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Get it on as or against 25 of the greatest boxers of all time! Includes Oscar De La Hoya, Sugar Ray Leonard, Evander Holyfield, and THE GREATEST, Muhammad Ali! Arcade-style Slugfest and Career modes. Super KO punches and hidden moves. Knockdown-dragout battles with the greatest boxers ever. Build a champion and fight to the top in Career mode. Pit current champs vs. legendary superstars, or challenge your created boxer against the greats.</desc>
          <image>./images/Knockout Kings 2000 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19991003T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Black Ops</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="262" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (USA)</name>
          <desc>Kirby&#39;s first 3-D adventure is also his Nintendo 64 debut, and it finds the always-versatile hero battling a new enemy called Dark Matter. Dark Matter is after a distant land&#39;s powerful crystal, but a young fairy named Ribbon attempts to save it by escaping with the gem to Dream Land. Now the crystal has been broken, and it&#39;s scattered around the world. Take control of Kirby and help him journey across six worlds, battling a wide variety of enemies and challenging bosses, as he tries to collect all 100 pieces of the shattered crystal.</desc>
          <image>./images/Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate></releasedate>
          <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="271" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Major League Baseball Featuring Ken Griffey Jr. (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Major League Baseball featuring Ken Griffey Jr. (USA)</name>
          <desc>Make your dreams of becoming a Major Leaguer a reality! Hit a grand slam, pitch a no-hitter, go for the cycle and steal home - all in the same game! If that&#39;s not enough, check out the real-time stat tracking in over 30 major categories. Improve your team by making the right trades and picking up the best free agents. Major League Baseball Featuring Ken Griffey Jr. is so real, every pitch counts!</desc>
          <image>./images/Major League Baseball Featuring Ken Griffey Jr. (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19980531T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Angel Studios</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="" source="">
          <path>./Mario Kart 64 (U) [h1C].v64</path>
          <name>Mario Kart 64 (U) [h1C]</name>
          <desc></desc>
          <releasedate></releasedate>
          <developer></developer>
          <publisher></publisher>
          <genre></genre>
      </game>
      <game id="961" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Pilotwings 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Pilotwings 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Forget about those other flying games.  This is the ultimate flight experience!  Pilotwings 64 carries you off into a vast three-dimensional environment.  Pilot several different vehicles and take in breathtaking sights.  Successfully complete flight tests to earn your flight badge.  Get a high enough score, and you’ll get a chance at bonus games such as Cannonball and Sky Diving!  Soar into a wild blue yonder with Pilotwings 64!&#xA;&#xA;* Tons of aerial challenges for you to master!&#xA;* Hop into the seat of a Gyrocopter and fire off some missiles!&#xA;* Strap on a Rocket Belt and check out places like Mt. Rushmore, the Space Needle and the Statue of Liberty!&#xA;* Dangle in silent solitude from a Hang GLider as you soar above tropical jungles and frozen ice floes.&#xA;* Save your progress in memory.</desc>
          <image>./images/Pilotwings 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.9</rating>
          <releasedate>19960623T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1143" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mischief Makers (U) (V1.0) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mischief Makers (USA)</name>
          <desc>Professor Theo has been kidnapped by the imperial forces of the evil empire. Now his robotic personal assistant, Marina Liteyears, must save the day! Marina will get some help from the troops who have remained loyal to King Aster. With their help, she&#39;ll grab, shake and throw her way to the Professor! Besides rescuing the Professor, Marina will also join in the effort to rebel against that nasty, horrible and evil empire. So, Grab a controller and help our Super Heroine shake up the evil empire!</desc>
          <image>./images/Mischief Makers (U) (V1.0) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.66667</rating>
          <releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Treasure</developer>
          <publisher>Enix</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="2914" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./NFL Blitz 2001 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>NFL Blitz 2001 (USA)</name>
          <desc>All of the big plays and bone-crunching hits of the arcade game can be put in the palm of your hand with NFL BLITZ 2001. As with all BLITZ games, football has been reduced to a high-scoring seven-on-seven affair. Pick your squad from any of the 31 NFL teams and go at it in the Season or Arcade modes. Arcade mode has you challenge all of the teams in the league to a game, while Season mode puts you through the paces of a 16-game season, the playoffs, and a chance to win the Super Bowl. No matter what mode you play, you won&#39;t miss a second of the action thanks to the multiple camera angles that are available. Whenever there is a great play, the digitized voice of the announcer will let you know, and you will be treated to a full-motion video sequence. Get into the game with NFL BLITZ 2001.</desc>
          <image>./images/NFL Blitz 2001 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20000912T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Midway Games</developer>
          <publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="20265" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mystical Ninja 2 Starring Goemon (E) (M3) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mystical Ninja 2 Starring Goemon (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</name>
          <desc>Goemon and all his friends are back in his greatest adventure yet! Goemon&#39;s Great Adventure combines classic Goemon platform action with an all-new twist. The evil time-traveling nun, Bismaru, has summoned Dochuki, a demon prince, to take over the Earth. But first, she wants to marry him! Can Goemon and his gang stop the demon? Can Dochuki escape the cloying clutches of the wacked-out nun? Will Ebisu ever beat his own dumpling eating record? It&#39;s an adventure you&#39;ll never forget!</desc>
          <image>./images/Mystical Ninja 2 Starring Goemon (E) (M3) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.65</rating>
          <releasedate>19990618T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1137" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mario Tennis (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mario Tennis (USA)</name>
          <desc>All of your favorite characters hit the court in a wild and wacky multiplayer tennis game from the makers of Mario Golf. Mario, Luigi, Bowser, Peach, Toad, and Donkey Kong lead off the all-star, 14-player line-up. The fast-paced action will have you unleashing vicious volleys, life-saving lobs, ballistic backhands and electrifying super-charged smashes!</desc>
          <image>./images/Mario Tennis (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6599999999999999</rating>
          <releasedate>20000721T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1147" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mortal Kombat 4 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mortal Kombat 4 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Shao Kahn has been defeated at the hands of Earth&#39;s warriors, and now Shinnok has escaped to his confines in the Netherealm. The war has resumed once again. This time, the battle CAN be won by mortals!</desc>
          <image>./images/Mortal Kombat 4 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19980623T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Eurocom Ent.</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1169" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./NHL 99 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>NHL 99 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The most celebrated hockey game comes to the Nintendo 64. Battle along the boards, feed the open man, patrol the ice! Game Features: *Beginner lever - pick up and play!; *Coaching strategies from Stanley Cup Winner Marc Crawford; *Commentary by Bill Clement; *5 game modes; *18 top international teams; *Updated 1998 roster-expansion Nashville Predators.</desc>
          <image>./images/NHL 99 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19981001T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="269" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Madden NFL 2002 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Madden NFL 2002 (USA)</name>
          <desc>#1 for a reason! Return to glory: Relive the golden days of 16-bit Madden gameplay in Madden Classic mode. Kick off the season with the newest NFL team: Take the field with all 32 NFL teams including the expansion Houston Texans. A game within a game: Run or defend an improved 2-Minute Drill, now featuring Head-To-Head Challenge. Bang-Boom-Pow: Perfect the X&#39;s and O&#39;s with the help of John Madden in Training mode.</desc>
          <image>./images/Madden NFL 2002 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>20010912T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Budcat</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1179" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Penny Racers (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Penny Racers (USA)</name>
          <desc>The premise of PENNY RACERS is simple: race your car the best you can and be among the top three to reach the checkered flag. To achieve this objective, you must avoid missiles launched by your competitors, among other things. One way to counter this is the barrel roll maneuver, which is a quick and effective way to avoid unexpected hurdles on the tracks. In the beginning, you drive a pretty unimpressive racer. However, if you beat the competition and place in the top three, your reward is the chance to upgrade your car. Be merciless and steal the losing racers&#39; special features, such as engine and armor upgrades, special attack abilities, and enhancing cosmetic features for the car. You have 13 different racer body styles and nine tracks to choose from. The cartoony racers zip through city streets, ice caves, and a volcano, and with the Track Create mode, you can design the wildest track you can imagine. When you toss four-player racing into the fray, the fun quadruples as the action intensifies and the losers are utterly humiliated.</desc>
          <image>./images/Penny Racers (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19990210T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Takara</developer>
          <publisher>THQ</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="2807" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (USA)</name>
          <desc>The NBA like you&#39;ve never seen it before! NBA Showtime: NBA on NBC brings you the top players from each team in a heart-pounding, pulse-racing above-the-rim match-up! You&#39;ll see the intensity on their faces and hear it in their voices, you&#39;ll feel the power of every pass and every shot! This is what the NBA is all about! Go for rebounds and 3-pointers in all 28 arenas around the league. Choose from over 130 real NBA players plus hidden characters!</desc>
          <image>./images/NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Eurocom Entertainment Software</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="270" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mario Party 2 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mario Party 2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Mario and the gang are back for another round of Bowser-bashin&#39; party action! Watch as your favorite Nintendo characters don different duds for each of the five all-new Adventure Boards! A slew of new tricks and devices bring new levels of challenge and excitement to board game play. New board maps, new Mini-Games, new action and new surprises means a whole new batch of fun! Get ready to unleash your best Hip Drops, hammer swings and high-flying high junks for another round of frenzied multi-player action!</desc>
          <image>./images/Mario Party 2 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>1</rating>
          <releasedate>19991217T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="" source="">
          <path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time - Master Quest (E) (GC) [f3].v64</path>
          <name>Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time - Master Quest (E) (GC) [f3]</name>
          <desc></desc>
          <releasedate></releasedate>
          <developer></developer>
          <publisher></publisher>
          <genre></genre>
      </game>
      <game id="1152" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon (USA)</name>
          <desc>A giant UFO has appeared over Oedo Castle, and the Mystical Ninja is off to save the world again! Control Goemon and his giant robot, Impact, Ebisimaru, a truly twisted ninja, Yae, the part-time militant mermaid, and Sasuke, a mechanical warrior. This brave band must travel from town to town, collecting information and purchasing helpful items in their quest to defeat the dreaded Peach Mountain Shoguns.</desc>
          <image>./images/Mystical Ninja Starring Goemon (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.56667</rating>
          <releasedate>19980416T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1149" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mortal Kombat Trilogy (U) (V1.2) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mortal Kombat Trilogy (USA) (Rev B)</name>
          <desc>Shao Kahn&#39;s final attempt to control the earth is upon us... 26 immediately playable characters plus 4 hidden characters! The new Aggressor Kombat Mode arms the quick and merciless with more strength and power to inflict heavy, damaging combinations! Over 30 moves and &#34;-Alities&#34; never seen in the arcade. New Brutalities let you pound opponents &#39;til they explode! New 3-on-3 Kombat Mode delivers a marathon fight-to-the-finish! 7 humiliating Stage Fatalities that send defeated opponents plummeting out of the arena to a grizzly death!</desc>
          <image>./images/Mortal Kombat Trilogy (U) (V1.2) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.23332999999999998</rating>
          <releasedate>19961031T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Midway</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1160" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./NBA Jam 2000 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>NBA Jam 2000 (USA)</name>
          <desc>All-new 2-on-2 JAM mode featuring 50 dunks and awesome special effects! Custom 2-on-2 JAM mode courts, including street court. Authentic 5-on-5 simulation mode with actual team play styles like the Jazz Pick-and-Roll. Jaw-dropping ultra high-rez graphics! Unique signature moves like the crossover dribble. Create your own JAM player. All 29 teams and over 300 NBA superstars! Over 800 all-new motion captured moves by the &#34;X-Man&#34; Xavier McDaniel!</desc>
          <image>./images/NBA Jam 2000 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.4</rating>
          <releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Acclaim</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1166" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./NFL Quarterback Club 99 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>NFL Quarterback Club 99 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The #1 football game on N64 just got a whole lot better! All 31 NFL teams, 3D rendered stadiums and over 1,500 players. Authentic team playbooks like the 49ers West Coast Defense and Steelers Ground Attack. All-new artificial intelligence developed by New York Jets offensive coordinator Charlie Weis. 250 all-new motion captured animations. Award-winning hi-rez graphics. Create your own players, coaches, teams, uniforms and playbooks!</desc>
          <image>./images/NFL Quarterback Club 99 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19981110T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Acclaim</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="42" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mario Party (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mario Party (USA)</name>
          <desc>Every game in the main series has a standard Party Mode in which up to four players play through a board, trying to collect as many stars as possible. In every turn, each player rolls a die and progresses on the board, which usually has branching paths. Coins are primarily earned by performing well in a minigame played at the end of each turn. On most boards, players earn stars by reaching a star space and purchasing a star for a certain amount of coins. The star space appears randomly on one of several pre-determined locations and moves every time a star is purchased, usually occupying a blue space.&#xA;Every Mario Party contains at least 50 to almost 110 minigames with a few different types. Four-player games are a free-for-all in which players compete individually. In 2-on-2 and 1-on-3 minigames, players compete as two groups, cooperating to win, even though they are still competing individually in the main game. Some minigames in Mario Party are 4-player co-op, even though it doesn&#39;t say it. In most situations, winners earn ten coins each.</desc>
          <image>./images/Mario Party (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6333300000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>19981214T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="960" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mario Party 3 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mario Party 3 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Mario Party 3 is the third and final Mario Party title for the Nintendo 64. A total of eight characters are available to choose from: Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, Yoshi, Wario, Donkey Kong, and newcomers Waluigi and Princess Daisy. Mario Party 3 features duel maps, in which two players try to lower each other&#39;s stamina to zero using non-playable characters such as Chain Chomps. It is the first Mario Party game to feature Luigi&#39;s main voice and also it is last Mario game where Princess Daisy appears in a yellow and white dress, and with long hair, as well as the last Mario game (until New Super Mario Bros. Wii) in which Yoshi&#39;s &#34;record-scratching&#34; voice is used. It is also the first Mario Party game to have multiple save slots.</desc>
          <image>./images/Mario Party 3 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8333299999999999</rating>
          <releasedate>20001207T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1155" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./NBA Courtside 2 - Featuring Kobe Bryant (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>NBA Courtside 2 featuring Kobe Bryant (USA)</name>
          <desc>NBA Courtside 2 Featuring Kobe Bryant is the sequel to Kobe Bryant in NBA Courtside and features NBA star Kobe Bryant on its cover. Bryant also performed the motion capture for the game. The ability to play multiple seasons has been added. New features include the ability to play a three-point contest and additional options for creating a player from scratch. The game features improved artificial intelligence helps to improve the realism of the gameplay. New dunk styles are possible to implement and enhanced motion capturing allows the no-look pass to be used during gameplay. There are more than 300 players and games can either be a realistic simulation of actual NBA action or a full-blown arcade experience. Plays such as the isolation play, the post up, and the triangle offense can be called.</desc>
          <image>./images/NBA Courtside 2 - Featuring Kobe Bryant (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19991108T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Left Field Productions</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="5469" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Mario Golf (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mario Golf</name>
          <desc>Since Mario rescued Princess Peach in Super Mario 64, he&#39;s been thoroughly enjoying his free time. Bowser hasn&#39;t been causing too much trouble, so Mario and his friends have decided to take a trip to the golf course. Waialae Country Club wouldn&#39;t allow a couple of underdressed plumbers to become members, so they&#39;ve come up with their own golf game for Nintendo 64. &#xA;&#xA;Mario Golf 64 features an all-star line up of 10 golfers from Nintendo&#39;s cast of video game celebrities, including Mario, Luigi, and Princess Peach. Each golfer has an individual set of strengths and weaknesses. A highlight of Mario Golf 64 is a special &amp;quot;Time Attack Mode,&amp;quot; where players must compete to finish a round of golf as quickly as possible. &#xA;&#xA;Mario Golf 64 features an impressive line-up of six courses, which means you&#39;ll have to master a total of 108 holes. An optional &amp;quot;Club Handicap Mode&amp;quot; ensures that you stay close to the competition, so Luigi won&#39;t get too frustrated if he falls behind. Even though the golfers are cartoons, the physics are as realistic as possible. The CPU calculates the exact ball movement based on wind direction, the strength of the strike, and any spin you may choose to place on the ball.</desc>
          <image>./images/Mario Golf (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19990630T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Camelot Software</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo - Camelot Software Planning</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1199" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./San Francisco Rush - Extreme Racing (U) (M3) (V1.0) [!].v64</path>
          <name>San Francisco Rush - Extreme Racing (USA) (En,Fr,De)</name>
          <desc>San Francisco Rush: Extreme Racing is the first game in the Rush series.&#xA;Tne N64 version contains six regular tracks and two hidden tracks. The regular tracks can be run in either reverse or mirrored modes and feature added collectible hidden keys throughout the track that can be used to unlock hidden vehicles. It also contains a Practice Mode and a Death Race mode where the game ends if the player crashes. The N64 port of Rush also includes a Circuit Mode and a save system for Fast Times, circuit progress, and hidden keys that the player can find on secret spots to unlock new cars.</desc>
          <image>./images/San Francisco Rush - Extreme Racing (U) (M3) (V1.0) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19971108T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Atari</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="161" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (U) (V1.2) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev B)</name>
          <desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule.  He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce.  As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf’s evil schemes.  Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora’s Domain.  Before you complete this epic quest, you’ll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.&#xA;&#xA;* The immersive storyline and environments draw players into an amazing 3D world.&#xA;* Time travel allows you to play as Link in different stages of his life.&#xA;* New gameplay features include a unique targeting system and 1st and 3rd person perspectives.&#xA;* Up to three games can be saved simultaneously to memory!</desc>
          <image>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (U) (V1.2) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.82955</rating>
          <releasedate>19981121T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1138" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Megaman 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Mega Man 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Mega Man Volnutt is the game&#39;s playable character. Mega Man Volnutt is a &#34;Digger&#34;, a person in charge of investigating ruins from a flooded Earth. During his journey with his friends, their ship crashes in Kattelox Island, where Mega Man decides to confront pirates who are attacking it to obtain the its hidden treasure. As an action roleplaying game, Mega Man Legends&#39;s gameplay is very different from the ones of the original series despite sharing a few elements.</desc>
          <image>./images/Megaman 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20001122T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1194" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Rocket - Robot on Wheels (E) (M3) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Rocket - Robot on Wheels (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</name>
          <desc>First-time Nintendo 64 developer Sucker Punch Studios jumped onto the scene with a highly original 3D platformer. The design philosophy behind the title is simple -- rather than build the platformer around the main character, the software house opted instead to focus on the interactivity of the 3D environments he travels. To that end, Rocket employs an advanced physics engine which allows the main character, a lovable unicycle-based robot named Rocket, to travel and experiment with colorful, platform-esque worlds with realistic gravity and inertia. Every object has its own set of lifelike attributes that must be &#34;weighed&#34; into consideration when solving puzzles.</desc>
          <image>./images/Rocket - Robot on Wheels (E) (M3) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19951115T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sucker Punch</developer>
          <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="173" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Perfect Dark (U) (V1.1) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev A)</name>
          <desc>Step into the Dark... As Carrington Institute&#39;s most promising new Agent, Joanna Dark must uncover the truth behind the dataDyne Corporation&#39;s recent technological breakthroughs - breakthroughs which could have serious consequences for mankind.</desc>
          <image>./images/Perfect Dark (U) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7583300000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="175" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora&#39;s Mask (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Legend of Zelda, The - Majora&#39;s Mask (USA)</name>
          <desc>Link’s all-new epic adventure lands him in the mystical world of Termina, where ever-present clocks count down the hours until a menacing moon falls from the sky above.  When his horse and Ocarina are stolen by a strange, masked figure, Link embarks on an urgent quest to solve the mystery of the moon, save the world from destruction, and find his way back to the peaceful land of Hyrule!&#xA;&#xA;* Link transforms before your eyes--Over 20 magical masks give Link powers and abilities he’s never had before!  Watch him transform into a hapless Deku child, a mighty Goron hero and a legendary Zora guitarist.&#xA;* Race against time--Characters and events flow with the hours of the day.  Set your own schedule and even alter time itself in a race to stop the moon and save the world!&#xA;* Panoramic environments!  Powered-up action battles!  Fully interactive characters and events!  Experience gorgeous rendered landscapes, swarms of attacking enemies and a deep, engrossing world of wonders with the power of the N64 Expansion Pak.</desc>
          <image>./images/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora&#39;s Mask (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.775</rating>
          <releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1202" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Snowboard Kids (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Snowboard Kids (USA)</name>
          <desc>The kids are arguing about their snowboarding skills. The debate escalates to the point where they decide to hold a snowboarding tournament to determine who is the best. One character, Shinobin, has no involvement whatsoever until he is unlocked by the player.&#xA;&#xA;In addition to the usual gameplay of a snowboarding game, Snowboard Kids adds &#34;Shots&#34; (special weapons used to attack players) and items which can help the player, hinder other players, or both.&#xA;&#xA;The game has nine main courses. Although some of the courses are snowy mountains, many are courses that would be unorthodox for snowboarding in the real world. Such courses include an amusement park, a desert, a vast valley, a dark highway, and a Japanese village during the cherry blossom festival.&#xA;&#xA;There were several game mechanics that were unique to Snowboard Kids from other snowboard games and racing games at the time. One was the addition of the second item slot, allowing each player to carry a shooting item and support item (such as a rock, or invisibility) at the same time. Also, players needed to pay 100 gold in order to grab an item during the race, which could be obtained either through performing tricks or collecting coins scattered across the course. All courses also required players to race down the hill for multiple laps. Once a player had reached the bottom of the hill, he or she would need to pass through the lift gate to be transported back to the top of the hill, and could not be attacked by other players in this transition.</desc>
          <image>./images/Snowboard Kids (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19980503T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Racdym</developer>
          <publisher>Atlus</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="216" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Super Mario 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Super Mario 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3-D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive sound track, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It&#39;s packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis - Bowser, King of the Koopas!</desc>
          <image>./images/Super Mario 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76875</rating>
          <releasedate>19960623T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="141" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Paper Mario (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Paper Mario (USA)</name>
          <desc>Mario pals around in an all-new action adventure! Mario&#39;s back in his first adventure since Super Mario 64, and this time, Bowser&#39;s bent on preventing a storybook ending. When Princess Peach is kidnapped, Mario plots to rescue the seven Star Spirits and rid the Mushroom Kingdom of Koopa&#39;s cruel cohorts. As he travels from the tropical jungles of Lavalava Island to the frosty heights of Shiver Mountain, he&#39;ll meet up with seven all-new companions... and he&#39;ll need help from each one or there&#39;ll be no happily ever after.</desc>
          <image>./images/Paper Mario (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76667</rating>
          <releasedate>20010205T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1195" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./RR64 - Ridge Racer 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>RR64 - Ridge Racer 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Ridge Racer makes its first appearance on a Nintendo console, including all of the fast, pick up and play action previously seen in the series on Playstation and in arcades.&#xA;&#xA;RR64 includes three tracks, each with three variations, making a total of nine tracks to get through. 25 cars are on offer, each with different power and speed abilities.&#xA;&#xA;Single player and multiplayer modes are included. Beat the clock and get to the finish line first to win.</desc>
          <image>./images/RR64 - Ridge Racer 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20000214T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Namco</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1197" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Rush 2 - Extreme Racing USA (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Rush 2 - Extreme Racing USA (USA)</name>
          <desc>Rush 2: Extreme Racing USA is a sequel to San Francisco Rush and the second game in the Rush series.&#xA;The game is notable for the high level of detail in the recreations of the various cities and states used, and for its fast arcade-style physics. The game also features a two-player mode and rumble pack support. Hidden shortcuts and jumps add to the replay value of the game.&#xA;Cities used are New York (Uptown and Downtown), Hawaii, Las Vegas, San Francisco (Alcatraz), Los Angeles, and Seattle. Other tracks playable at the start of the game are Stunt, Crash, and Halfpipe. A bonus track can be won where your car is miniaturized and you drive through the offices of Midway Games. Another bonus is the full pipe level, as the last achievement to unlock.</desc>
          <image>./images/Rush 2 - Extreme Racing USA (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19981110T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Atari</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Star Fox 64 (U) (V1.1) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev A)</name>
          <desc>The Lylat system has been invaded!  Join Fox McCloud and his Star Fox team as they fight to save the galaxy from the clutches of the evil Andross.  Travel to many different 3-D worlds.  Battle the enemy in the air and on the ground and listen in as Fox McCloud interacts with a cast of characters.&#xA;&#xA;See how it feels to feel what you see!  The N64 Rumble Pak controller accessory instantly transmits all the bumps and blasts during the action.  It’s a new jolt to your game play experience!&#xA;&#xA;* Four Players compete simultaneously in Vs. mode!&#xA;* Game Pak memory saves the top 10 scores!&#xA;* Outstanding cinema scenes tell the Star Fox saga!</desc>
          <image>./images/Star Fox 64 (U) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.78</rating>
          <releasedate>19970427T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1203" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Snowboard Kids 2 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Snowboard Kids 2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The game is set in Snow Town, which is the main hometown of the protagonists. The plot follows the daily lives and adventures of the kids, and the rather ridiculous attempts of Damien to sabotage them.&#xA;&#xA;The gameplay of this game is almost identical to its predecessor&#39;s, but with a few differences.&#xA;&#xA;There are now three distinct playing modes: the Story mode, which follows the game plot and uses the classical system of cash prizes by winning the races; the battle mode, which includes multiplayer mode; and the Training mode.&#xA;&#xA;There were new additions and changes to the Items and Shots. All of them were redesigned and the Shots were renamed as Weapons. Additions include the Rocket, the Wings and the Whirlwind (see more below). Other changes to the Items and Weapons include the reduction in the freeze time when a character is hit by the Freezing Shot, and the effect of losing coins when hit by a Slapstick.&#xA;&#xA;The special tricks (which were different for each character and required the player to perform a combo to do them) were replaced by the ability of doing multiple tricks while in the air. It also added the ability to repel Weapon attacks by performing a Trick or Board Grab in the imminence of the hit. The player can also look behind by pressing the R button.</desc>
          <image>./images/Snowboard Kids 2 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19990302T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Racdym</developer>
          <publisher>Atlus</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="5682" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Virtual Pro Wrestling 64 (J) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Virtual Pro Wrestling 64 (Japan)</name>
          <desc>Virtual Pro Wrestling 64 is a video game released in 1997 on the Nintendo 64 game console. The game was only released in Japan. Developed by the same people who made WCW vs. nWo: World Tour, the game is very similar to its American counterpart. The game i</desc>
          <image>./images/Virtual Pro Wrestling 64 (J) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Asmik Ace Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
          <publisher>AKI Corporation</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="962" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Road Rash 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Road Rash 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>180 MPH slap in the face, anyone? Multi-player modes for up to four players including Deathmatch, Cop Mode and Tag. New weapons and moves like the dreaded spoke jam. Intense pack brawling, including grudges and alliances. 200 miles of interconnected tracks and environments. Over 25 bikes and characters to choose from. Thrashin&#39; soundtrack featuring Sugar Ray, The Mermen and more!</desc>
          <image>./images/Road Rash 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19990922T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Pacific Coast Power and Light</developer>
          <publisher>THQ</publisher>
          <genre>Vehicle Simulation</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="411" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Wave Race 64 (U) (V1.1) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Wave Race 64 (USA) (Rev A)</name>
          <desc>Wave Race 64 is sure to provide some of the most exciting racing you&#39;ve ever experienced. Feel the pounding and crashing of the waves as you accelerate into straight-aways, whip around the marker buoys and go airborne on the jump ramps. Don&#39;t race alone - challenge a friend! Take control in three different modes of play - Championship, Time Trials and Stunt Mode. Nine challenging courses set in exotic locales - race conditions change and the wave action responds to the way both you and your opponents race!</desc>
          <image>./images/Wave Race 64 (U) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.68571</rating>
          <releasedate>19960927T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nintendo</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="405" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Tetrisphere (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Tetrisphere (USA)</name>
          <desc>Tetrisphere is a variant on Tetris in which various shapes are shifted across a wrapped three-dimensional grid resembling a sphere, and then destroyed. The objective of the game changes depending on the mode, but generally consists of removing layers of shapes to reach the playing field&#39;s core. Despite very little domestic advertising, Tetrisphere enjoyed moderately good sales and a mostly favorable critical reception. Reviewers praised the game&#39;s originality and the musical score composed by Neil D. Voss.</desc>
          <image>./images/Tetrisphere (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19970811T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>H20 Interactive</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Puzzle</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="5662" source="screenscraper.fr">
          <path>./Virtual Pro Wrestling 2 (J) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Virtual Pro Wrestling 2 - Oudou Keishou (Japan)</name>
          <desc></desc>
          <image>./images/Virtual Pro Wrestling 2 (J) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.85</rating>
          <releasedate>20000128T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Asmik Ace Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
          <publisher>AKI Corporation</publisher>
          <genre>Fight</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="413" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./WinBack - Covert Operations (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>WinBack - Covert Operations (USA)</name>
          <desc>A terrorist group calling itself the Crying Lions is about to take over the world with its mighty satellite and Jean-Luc Cougar is the only one who can stop it. As Jean-Luc, a covert operative working for the Strategic Covert Actions Team, you are responsible for taking back a Lions-controlled base and regaining power of the satellite. Some of the weapons you&#39;ll have to acquire and use to defeat the terrorists are handguns, shotguns, and machine guns, though you&#39;ll also need to access such materials as explosives, detectors, flashlights and medical kits in order to succeed. A refreshing take on the traditional action game, WINBACK requires as much stealth and strategy as it does reflexes and use of weaponry. The game features six different multiplayer modes, supporting up to four players: Death Match, Lethal Tag, Quick Draw, Cube Hunt, Team Battle, and Point Match. You select your difficulty level and you can even start off in a Tutorial mode to get the controls down.</desc>
          <image>./images/WinBack - Covert Operations (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.4</rating>
          <releasedate>19991020T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Omega Force</developer>
          <publisher>Koei</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="403" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (U) (M3) (V1.0) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA)</name>
          <desc>Fly against the evil Empire! As Luke Skywalker, co-founder of the Rebel Alliance&#39;s elite Rogue Squadron, you must combat the evil Galactic Empire! Engage in intense, fast-paced planetary air-to-ground and air-to-air missions - dogfights, search and destroy, reconnaissance, bombing runs, rescue assignments and more! Pilot X-wings, Y-wings, A-wings, V-wings and Snowspeeders with powerful weapons in over 15 missions battling TIE fighters, TIE bombers, Imperial shuttles, AT-AT walkers, AT-STs and other challenging foes.</desc>
          <image>./images/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (U) (M3) (V1.0) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19981203T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Factor 5</developer>
          <publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1176" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (J) (V1.1) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (Japan) (Rev A)</name>
          <desc>Ogre Battle 64 is the third game in the series, the first two being Ogre Battle: The March of the Black Queen, and Tactics Ogre: Let Us Cling Together.&#xA;The story follows Magnus Gallant, a recent graduate of the Ischka Military Academy, and fledgling captain in Palatinus&#39; Southern region, Alba. As civil war erupts in the country, Magnus eventually decides to join the revolution with its leader, Frederick Raskin, first liberating the southern region with the Zenobians&#39; aid, then Nirdam and uniting with them, then returning the Eastern Region of Capitrium to the Orthodox church, and finally marching on the capital of Latium. However, along the way, Magnus&#39; battalion, the Blue Knights, finds its enemies escalating, from the puppet kingdom of Palatinus, to the might of the Holy Lodis Empire, to the Dark Hordes of the Netherworld.</desc>
          <image>./images/Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (J) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.64</rating>
          <releasedate>20001007T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Quest</developer>
          <publisher>Atlus</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="417" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./WWF WrestleMania 2000 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>WWF WrestleMania 2000 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The greatest wrestling game ever created! Tons of game modes, including Cage Match, Road to Wrestlemania, Create a PPV, and more! Create and bet WWF Championship belts with your friends. Over 50 of the top WWF superstars, more than any other WWF game! Thousands of signature moves, taunts, and mannerisms. New Create a Wrestler, with custom moves, costumes, and fighting styles!</desc>
          <image>./images/WWF WrestleMania 2000 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.825</rating>
          <releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Aki Corp.</developer>
          <publisher>THQ</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="30094" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Shadow Man (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Shadow Man (USA)</name>
          <desc>You&#39;re the Shadow Man, a person who can switch between the world of the dead and of the living. In Shadow Man your mission is to prevent 5 serial killers from bringing the total armageddon. In the world of the living, you&#39;re mortal and have conventional weapons. When you die, you are transported to the world of the dead and you become Shadow Man once again. Which means you&#39;re not really mortal. In the world of the dead you can&#39;t use normal weapons, your gun shoots ghosts which kill the zombies and the other ugly creatures which live there. You also have different voodoo powers and weapons. And you&#39;re carrying a large inventory around.</desc>
          <image>./images/Shadow Man (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8</rating>
          <releasedate>19990731T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Acclaim</developer>
          <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="414" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./World Driver Championship (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>World Driver Championship (USA)</name>
          <desc>One of the last racing simulations to be released for Nintendo 64, this graphically intensive title used custom microcode optimization and high polygon count modelling. The development team was able to optimize the usage of the various processors within the N64 to allow far draw distance (reducing the need for fog or pop-up), high detail texturing and models, Doppler effect audio, and advanced lighting and fog effects for realistic weather conditions. Impressively the game has a high resolution 640x480 mode that does not require the add-on N64 RAM Expansion Pak. Additionally, unlike many other games of its type on the platform, the game runs high resolution at a sufficiently playable pace, undoubtedly due to the use of a reduced screen area letterbox mode that lessens the number of pixels needing to be displayed.</desc>
          <image>./images/World Driver Championship (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19990616T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Boss Game Studios</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="404" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Super Smash Bros. (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Super Smash Bros. (USA)</name>
          <desc>It&#39;s a Bumpin&#39;, Bruisin&#39;, Brawlin&#39; Bash! The many worlds of Nintendo collide in the ultimate showdown of strength and skill! Up to four players can choose their favorite characters - complete with signature attacks - and go at it in Team Battles and Free-For-Alls. Or venture out on your own to conquer the 14 stages in single-player mode. Either way, Super Smash Bros. is a no-holds-barred action-fest that will keep you coming back for more!</desc>
          <image>./images/Super Smash Bros. (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.73333</rating>
          <releasedate>19990121T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1239" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./World Cup 98 (U) (M8) [!].v64</path>
          <name>World Cup 98 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Sv,Da)</name>
          <desc>The main feature of the game is the World Cup tournament itself, where the player may use either the actual groups used in the finals, or groups composed of a random selection of the included teams. Each match takes place in a recreation of the venue it was played in the actual tournament. As in the real tournament, group games do not go to extra time or a penalty shootout but knockout matches do.</desc>
          <image>./images/World Cup 98 (U) (M8) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19980518T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>EA Sports</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="1206" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Star Soldier - Vanishing Earth (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Star Soldier - Vanishing Earth (USA)</name>
          <desc>In the year 2098 mankind had been critically attacked by a military force from Zeograd, a hostile planet in a far off galaxy. Commander Parker Deehan of Special Interception Airforce (SIA) decided to deploy and pilot the F98 Star Soldier fighter craft into the front line of battle against Zeograd. Losing the battle meant the extinction of mankind and the total annihilation of Earth!</desc>
          <image>./images/Star Soldier - Vanishing Earth (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19981215T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
          <publisher>Electro Brain</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="416" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./WWF No Mercy (U) (V1.1) [!].v64</path>
          <name>WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev A)</name>
          <desc>Jump into the ring with the biggest, baddest jambronis around and experience brutal WWF action never before seen in a console game! Over 65 WWF superstars, all-new Ladder matches, and all-new Double-Team moves, like the Dudley 3D Deathdrop! Take on the entire Federation in Survival Mode. Take the action out of the ring in 10 different backstage areas!</desc>
          <image>./images/WWF No Mercy (U) (V1.1) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.775</rating>
          <releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Aki Corp.</developer>
          <publisher>THQ</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1237" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Wetrix (U) (M6) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Wetrix (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</name>
          <desc>A rainstorm so fierce, it will keep you from leaving your home for the next six months. Wetrix just might be the most addictive puzzle game of all time. Using randomly shaped 3D blocks as they fall from the sky, you must create a series of lakes and dams before the heavy rains appear. Because if the water drains, you lose! Sound simple? Well, mix in a few natural disasters and bomb attacks, and suddenly you need to muster all your strategy and skill to combat nature&#39;s fury!</desc>
          <image>./images/Wetrix (U) (M6) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19980601T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Zed Two</developer>
          <publisher>Ocean</publisher>
          <genre>Puzzle</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1236" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./WCW-nWo Revenge (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>WCW-nWo Revenge (USA)</name>
          <desc>More than 60 wrestlers, including ALL of the top WCW and NWO superstars! Awesome new features including wrestler entrances, all the real WCW belts, hidden weapons, instant replay, completely updated roster and complete user stats and arcade style scores! Enjoy real pay-per-view arenas, 40-man Battle Royale mode, and a costume editing feature!</desc>
          <image>./images/WCW-nWo Revenge (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7625</rating>
          <releasedate>19981026T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Aki Corp.</developer>
          <publisher>THQ</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1238" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Wipeout 64 (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Wipeout 64 (USA)</name>
          <desc>WipEout 64 was released by Psygnosis as a follow-up to the racing game WipEout XL, taking place one year later in 2098. Like in previous installments players control highspeed hovercrafts, pick up weapons to damage the opponents&#39; vehicles and try to finish the race in the first position. In many aspects, the gameplay is pretty similar to its predecessor, such as selection of hovercrafts, visuals or the handling system. Beside new racing tracks the main differences include a Split-Screen Multiplayer Mode (up to four players), Weapon &amp; Super Combo Challenges as well as various Special Weapons for each Team!</desc>
          <image>./images/Wipeout 64 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7833300000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>19981103T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Psygnosis Limited</developer>
          <publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="5652" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Sin and Punishment - Successor of the Earth (J).v64</path>
          <name>Tsumi to Batsu - Hoshi no Keishousha (Japan)</name>
          <desc>Earth is under threat from Ruffians - mutants bred to boost dwindling food stocks who have turned against their masters. As a young resistance fighter, face an onslaught of bio-genetic monsters and corrupt military forces in your battle to save the planet.&#xA;&#xA;For the first time outside of Japan, you can experience the non-stop action of this Nintendo 64 classic, created by the shoot em up masters at Treasure Co. Ltd.&#xA;&#xA;Battle across land, sea and sky; collect energy, time and point bonuses; rack up massive combos to earn extra continues; and face the wrath of enormous bosses. Plus - invite a friend to join in, controlling the gun sight while you move the character.</desc>
          <image>./images/Sin and Punishment - Successor of the Earth (J)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7428600000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>20001221T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Treasure</developer>
          <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="2952" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Spider-Man (U) [!].v64</path>
          <name>Spider-Man (USA)</name>
          <desc>Spider-Man is the first 3D game to star the popular web-slinger. It is loosely based on Spider-Man: The Animated Series and Spider-Man Unlimited and features some of the voice cast from each and similar character designs.&#xA;&#xA;Peter Parker is attending a demonstration of the reformed Dr. Otto Octavius&#39;s new invention when an imposter Spider-Man steals the device. Spider-Man must work to clear his name and uncover the sinister motives behind the device&#39;s theft.</desc>
          <image>./images/Spider-Man (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8</rating>
          <releasedate>20001121T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Neversoft Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
          <publisher>Activision</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
      </game>
  </gameList>