<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
      <game id="495" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Alundra/Alundra (USA) (v1.1).cue</path>
          <name>Alundra (USA) (v1.1)</name>
          <desc>Between the worlds of light and dark lies the world of dram. A world where the rule of reason loosens its grip. A place where an insidious evil is stealing minds and blackening the hearts of those from the world of light. Grab a weapon and become the dreamwalker Alundra as he struggles to purge the evil Id of an ancient world before it falls to ash.&#xA;&#xA;Explore dungeons, find monster butt as you weave between tense reality and nightmarish dreams to save the hapless masses. With a wide cast of characters and scores of challenging puzzles created by the people responsible for Landstalker on the Genesis. Alundra will rob you of precious sleep until you finish.</desc>
          <image>./images/Alundra (USA) (v1.1)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.65</rating>
          <releasedate>19971231T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Matrix Software</developer>
          <publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11560" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Ace Combat 2/Ace Combat 2 [SLUS-00404].cue</path>
          <name>Ace Combat 2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Superior enemy intelligence.&#xA;&#xA;We&#39;ve devised a weapon that&#39;s deadlier than a smart bomb. It&#39;s called a smart pilot. Now, Ace Combat 2 pits you against a whole squadron of them - 3-D polygon jet jocks that maneuver like the real deal; turning every scorching sortie and dogfight into a kill-or-be-killed situation. With nearly double the missions of its predecessor, you&#39;ll double your chances of taking out the enemy. (Or taking a heat-seeker up the exhaust.)&#xA;&#xA;The most realistic dogfights ever created for the PlayStation game console.&#xA;&#xA;-Total 3-D polygon environment - fly freely and unload your arsenal with reckless abandon.&#xA;-Advanced artificial intelligence - cunning and calculating enemy pilots.&#xA;-30 formidable missions - nearly double the missions of Air Combat.&#xA;-Awesome mission debriefings - dynamic diagrams and moving maps for surgical strikes.&#xA;-Secret planes and hidden missions - the better you fly, the more you&#39;ll reveal.</desc>
          <image>./images/Ace Combat 2 [SLUS-00404]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19970731T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Namco</developer>
          <publisher>Namco</publisher>
          <genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1541" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Arc the Lad/Arc the Lad.cue</path>
          <name>Arc the Lad Collection - Arc the Lad (USA)</name>
          <desc>A girl named Kukuru lives in a village controlled by the Sacred Tribe - people who guard an ancient flame which contains a powerful spirit that was sealed in it many years ago. Kukuru must marry a man she doesn&#39;t love, and in order to avoid this marriage, she accepts the offer of the mayor: he asks her to extinguish the flame. As a result, the spirit awakes and threatens to destroy the world. A young adventurer named Arc arrives to the village at the same moment as Kukuru is standing frightened in front of the spirit. Arc immediately recognizes it - it was the murderer of his father! Before he realizes how that could be possible, the spirit disappears, and now Arc and Kukuru have to do everything in their powers to undo the error, to stop the spirit, and perhaps to avenge the death of Arc&#39;s father.&#xA;&#xA;&#34;Arc the Lad&#34; is a hybrid of traditional and strategy-based console-style RPGs. The story unfolds as you are transported from location to location and enter battles - you don&#39;t walk around on the world map, choosing yourself which location to visit. The battles take place on a battle field, on which you can move and attack only when you approach the opponent.</desc>
          <image>./images/Arc the Lad-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate></releasedate>
          <developer>G-Craft</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="1543" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Arc the Lad 3/Arc the Lad 3 - Disk 1.cue</path>
          <name>Arc the Lad Collection - Arc the Lad III (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
          <desc>The events of this game take place several years after Elk and Arc faced their ultimate enemy in &#34;Arc the Lad II&#34;. You control Alec, a teenager whose entire village was destroyed by an unknown evil - an event that was later called &#34;The Great Disaster&#34;. He was saved by a mysterious Hunter. Since then, growing peacefully in a village he was brought to, which was like a new home for the survivors of the Great Disaster, Alec dreams about meeting the Hunter again, and becoming a Hunter himself. Together with his best friend Lutz he tries his luck in nearby towns, receiving small Hunter jobs, until the fate crosses the ways of the two young people with a mysterious organization called the Academy. And there their adventure really begins...&#xA;&#xA;The gameplay of this third installment of Arc the Lad series is very similar to that of the predecessor. You fight enemies in turn-based battles, and can move freely on the battlefield, positioning your party members the way you like. You can upgrade your weapons by forging them with special materials, and have a variety of techniques and magic spells at your disposal.</desc>
          <image>./images/Arc the Lad 3 - Disk 1-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19991028T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>G-Craft</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="2506" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Bloody Roar II/Bloody Roar II (USA).cue</path>
          <name>Bloody Roar II (USA)</name>
          <desc>Transform and do battle as a human-animal hybrid in this classic 3D fighting game! Put your strength to the test and fight your way to the top!&#xA;&#xA;The hook of the Bloody Roar series is that your combatants can transform into animalistic versions of themselves -- human-animal hybrids with a thirst for violence. During each round you can fight as a person or transform into a beast when your meter fills up. As an animal you&#39;ll have more moves at your disposal with which to destroy your opponent.</desc>
          <image>./images/Bloody Roar II (USA)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Eighting/Raizing</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1543" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Arc the Lad 3/Arc the Lad 3 - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Arc the Lad Collection - Arc the Lad III (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>The events of this game take place several years after Elk and Arc faced their ultimate enemy in &#34;Arc the Lad II&#34;. You control Alec, a teenager whose entire village was destroyed by an unknown evil - an event that was later called &#34;The Great Disaster&#34;. He was saved by a mysterious Hunter. Since then, growing peacefully in a village he was brought to, which was like a new home for the survivors of the Great Disaster, Alec dreams about meeting the Hunter again, and becoming a Hunter himself. Together with his best friend Lutz he tries his luck in nearby towns, receiving small Hunter jobs, until the fate crosses the ways of the two young people with a mysterious organization called the Academy. And there their adventure really begins...&#xA;&#xA;The gameplay of this third installment of Arc the Lad series is very similar to that of the predecessor. You fight enemies in turn-based battles, and can move freely on the battlefield, positioning your party members the way you like. You can upgrade your weapons by forging them with special materials, and have a variety of techniques and magic spells at your disposal.</desc>
          <image>./images/Arc the Lad 3 - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19991028T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>G-Craft</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="8375" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Bushido Blade/Bushido Blade (USA).cue</path>
          <name>Bushido Blade (USA)</name>
          <desc>&#34;Bushido&#34; is the soul of Japan - an ancient honor code deeply followed by samurai warriors for centuries. Plunge into real world battles across vast 3D environments that you can run, slice and tear through. Sword matches become unbelievably real where one critical blow is the mean difference between death and victory.&#xA;&#xA;Features:&#xA;* 1 &amp; 2 Player combat.&#xA;* 6 awesome fighting modes.&#xA;* 6 skilled warriors.&#xA;* 8 ancient swords and weapons.&#xA;* Plus unique sub-weapons.&#xA;* Countless special moves.</desc>
          <image>./images/Bushido Blade (USA)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.72</rating>
          <releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Light Weight</developer>
          <publisher>Square, SCEA</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="10862" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Armored Core - Project Phantasm/Armored Core - Project Phantasm.cue</path>
          <name>Armored Core - Project Phantasma (USA)</name>
          <desc>A Raven operating out of Isaac City receives an unusual request. Not only is the request both vague and cryptic, stating simply: &#34;Infiltrate the underground urban complex, Amber Crown,&#34;, but it also bypasses normal channels of communication and is sent directly to the Raven in question, without anyone else seeing the message. No sender name or corporate affiliation is mentioned, but the monetary reward promised is massive. Because of the amount, the mission will obviously be intensely dangerous, but Ravens aren&#39;t the type to shy away from any challenge. With interest piqued, the Raven climbs into the AC and heads toward Amber Crown.</desc>
          <image>./images/Armored Core - Project Phantasm-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>From Software</developer>
          <publisher>Agetec</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1005" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Chrono Cross/Chrono Cross - Disk 1.cue</path>
          <name>Chrono Cross (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
          <desc>Chrono Cross features standard RPG gameplay with some differences. Players advance the game by controlling the protagonist Serge through the game&#39;s world, primarily by foot and boat. Navigation between areas is conducted via an overworld map, much like Chrono Trigger&#39;s, depicting the landscape from a scaled down overhead view. Around the island world are villages, outdoor areas, and dungeons, through which the player moves in three dimensions. Locations such as cities and forests are represented by more realistically scaled field maps, in which players can converse with locals to procure items and services, solve puzzles and challenges, or encounter enemies. Like Chrono Trigger, the game features no random encounters; enemies are openly visible on field maps or lie in wait to ambush the party</desc>
          <image>./images/Chrono Cross - Disk 1-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76667</rating>
          <releasedate>19991118T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1005" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Chrono Cross/Chrono Cross - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Chrono Cross (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>Chrono Cross features standard RPG gameplay with some differences. Players advance the game by controlling the protagonist Serge through the game&#39;s world, primarily by foot and boat. Navigation between areas is conducted via an overworld map, much like Chrono Trigger&#39;s, depicting the landscape from a scaled down overhead view. Around the island world are villages, outdoor areas, and dungeons, through which the player moves in three dimensions. Locations such as cities and forests are represented by more realistically scaled field maps, in which players can converse with locals to procure items and services, solve puzzles and challenges, or encounter enemies. Like Chrono Trigger, the game features no random encounters; enemies are openly visible on field maps or lie in wait to ambush the party</desc>
          <image>./images/Chrono Cross - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76667</rating>
          <releasedate>19991118T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="8364" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Colony Wars 3/Colony Wars 3.cue</path>
          <name>Colony Wars - Red Sun (USA)</name>
          <desc>Red Sun is the third in Psygnosis&#39; Star Wars inspired &#34;Colony Wars&#34; saga. This time around you follow the personal quest of Valdmar a miner who gets caught up in the wars between the League and the Navy after meeting the enigmatic &#34;General&#34; in a series of mysterious dreams.</desc>
          <image>./images/Colony Wars 3-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20000502T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Psygnosis</developer>
          <publisher>Midway</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11574" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Command &amp; Conquer/Command &amp; Conquer [NOD Disc] [SLUS-00410].cue</path>
          <name>Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 2) (NOD)</name>
          <desc>Command &amp; Conquer develops ideas from Westwood&#39;s previous game Dune 2, forming a real-time strategy (RTS) game. The control system involves selecting units with the mouse and then directing them, while the opponents make their moves without waiting for a &#34;turn&#34; to end.&#xA;&#xA;The game focuses on a war between two organizations, The Brotherhood of Nod and the Global Defense Initiative. The player can take control of either side for more than 15 missions. Both have different units and structures, including artillery, tanks and light infantry.</desc>
          <image>./images/Command &amp; Conquer [NOD Disc] [SLUS-00410]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Westwood</developer>
          <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
          <genre>Strategy</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1007" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Crash Team Racing/Crash Team Racing [SCUS-94426].cue</path>
          <name>Crash Team Racing</name>
          <desc>The main antagonist of the story, Nitros Oxide, is the self-proclaimed fastest racer in the galaxy who threatens to turn Earth into a concrete parking lot. Preceding Oxide are four boss characters: Ripper Roo, a deranged straitjacket-wearing kangaroo; Papu Papu, the morbidly obese leader of the island&#39;s native tribe; Komodo Joe, a Komodo dragon with a speech sound disorder; and Pinstripe Potoroo, a greedy pinstripe-clad potoroo. The four boss characters, along with an imperfect and morally ambiguous clone of Crash Bandicoot named Fake Crash, become accessible as playable characters if the Adventure Mode is fully completed.</desc>
          <image>./images/Crash Team Racing [SCUS-94426]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
          <publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11534" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Darkstalkers 3/Darkstalkers 3.cue</path>
          <name>Darkstalkers 3 (USA)</name>
          <desc>This is the 3rd in the Darkstalkers series (the 2nd, Night Warriors: Darkstalkers&#39; Revenge, was published only for the Sega Saturn in the US.) It plays much the same as the first, but features better animation, more playable characters, and a deeper storyline.&#xA;&#xA;Jedah, the &#34;Lord of Vampire&#34;, has summoned all of the Night Warriors to his realm to be assimilated into his being. Of course, this serves as a great excuse to have more one-on-one fights...&#xA;&#xA;Play as Jedah, B. B. Hood, Q-Bee, Lilith, Demitri, Morrigan, Anakaris, Victor, L. Raptor, Hsien-Ko, J. Talbain, Felicia, Rikuo, Sasquatch, Bishamon, Donovan, Pyron or Huitzil, and conquer the enemy.</desc>
          <image>./images/Darkstalkers 3-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19981118T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="12770" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Deception III/Deception III.cue</path>
          <name>Deception III - Dark Delusion (USA)</name>
          <desc>Taken against her will to Alendar Kingdom, Layna who becomes your challenge is now under the control of the evil King Frederick. As her life wears thin, it becomes your sole mission to ensure Layna saves herself as King Frederick&#39;s mysterious organization attempts to bring Layna to her final doom. Through preparation of strategic trap setting you begin to plot and devise various techniques to destroy those who hold you captive. With over 2,000 trap variations it is up to you to choose the best combinations to assist you in conquering your enemy. Because there are multiple endings. Layna&#39;s final fate may be your worst nightmare or ultimate fantasy. The choice is yours. The options are endless.&#xA;&#xA;* Over 2,000 trap variations&#xA;* New and improved trap element system allows more freedom for players to develop traps.&#xA;* Advanced 3D Polygon Graphics with Third Person Perspective.&#xA;* Four modes of play are offered including the &#34;Scenario Mode&#34;, &#34;Trap License Mode&#34;, &#34;Free Training Mode&#34;, and the &#34;Expert Mode&#34;.&#xA;* Multiple endings!</desc>
          <image>./images/Deception III-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20000301T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tecmo</developer>
          <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
          <genre>Horror</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11041" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Dragon Warrior VII/Dragon Warrior VII - Disk 1.cue</path>
          <name>Dragon Warrior VII (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
          <desc>The story begins when the father of the protagonist brings home a map fragment from a fishing trip; this map suggests to the protagonist and his friend that the world had, at some point in its past, many continents, though now there is only the small island of Estard. The two of them find a way to travel back to the past, when the continents still existed. The continents are facing serious problems that threaten their existence; the protagonist and his growing party work to resolve the problems, and when they do, the continents reappear in the present. When all the continents are finally restored, the Demon Lord, who is responsible for the loss of many of the continents, appears and seals away many of the continents again. He then raises up his Dark Palace, where the party face the Demon Lord in a final showdown.</desc>
          <image>./images/Dragon Warrior VII - Disk 1-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20011101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Enix</developer>
          <publisher>Enix</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11041" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Dragon Warrior VII/Dragon Warrior VII - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Dragon Warrior VII (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>The story begins when the father of the protagonist brings home a map fragment from a fishing trip; this map suggests to the protagonist and his friend that the world had, at some point in its past, many continents, though now there is only the small island of Estard. The two of them find a way to travel back to the past, when the continents still existed. The continents are facing serious problems that threaten their existence; the protagonist and his growing party work to resolve the problems, and when they do, the continents reappear in the present. When all the continents are finally restored, the Demon Lord, who is responsible for the loss of many of the continents, appears and seals away many of the continents again. He then raises up his Dark Palace, where the party face the Demon Lord in a final showdown.</desc>
          <image>./images/Dragon Warrior VII - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20011101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Enix</developer>
          <publisher>Enix</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11440" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Ehrgeiz/Ehrgeiz - God Bless the Ring [NTSC-U] [SLUS-00809].cue</path>
          <name>Ehrgeiz - God Bless the Ring (USA)</name>
          <desc>BEYOND FIGHTING&#xA;&#xA;The world&#39;s most brutal tournament has its trophy the legendary weapon &#39;EHRGEIZ&#39;.&#xA;&#xA;Now, fighters from around the world assemble to claim this prize and its mysterious power.&#xA;&#xA;3 INTENSE PLAYING MODES:&#xA;Arcade Fighting Action&#xA;&#xA;* Over ten playable characters, a cast of hidden characters, and favorites from Final Fantasy VII.&#xA;* Complete 360 degree range of motion: battle hand-to-hand, with weapons, or with devastating combos and special moves.&#xA;* Multiple-level, fully interactive arenas.&#xA;&#xA;Challenging Mini-Games&#xA;* Compete in tests of speed, skill, and dexterity in any of four unique mini-games.&#xA;&#xA;Full-featured RPG Adventure&#xA;* Descend into ever-changing random dungeon layouts in search of treasure, ever-stronger weapons, and answers.</desc>
          <image>./images/Ehrgeiz - God Bless the Ring [NTSC-U] [SLUS-00809]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Dream Factory</developer>
          <publisher>Square</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="527" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy IX/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 1.cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy IX (USA) (Disc 1) (v1.0)</name>
          <desc>A band of thieves are hired to kidnap Princess Garnet of Alexandria. After they succeed, they end up becoming her guardians. And while protecting the fair Princess from a powerful evil...they hold the fate of the world in their hands. Play along on the epic journey filled with danger, mystery, war and love.</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 1-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.765</rating>
          <releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="527" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy IX/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy IX (USA) (Disc 2) (v1.0)</name>
          <desc>A band of thieves are hired to kidnap Princess Garnet of Alexandria. After they succeed, they end up becoming her guardians. And while protecting the fair Princess from a powerful evil...they hold the fate of the world in their hands. Play along on the epic journey filled with danger, mystery, war and love.</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.765</rating>
          <releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="527" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy IX/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 3.cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy IX (USA) (Disc 3) (v1.0)</name>
          <desc>A band of thieves are hired to kidnap Princess Garnet of Alexandria. After they succeed, they end up becoming her guardians. And while protecting the fair Princess from a powerful evil...they hold the fate of the world in their hands. Play along on the epic journey filled with danger, mystery, war and love.</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 3-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.765</rating>
          <releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="527" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy IX/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 4.cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy IX (USA) (Disc 4) (v1.0)</name>
          <desc>A band of thieves are hired to kidnap Princess Garnet of Alexandria. After they succeed, they end up becoming her guardians. And while protecting the fair Princess from a powerful evil...they hold the fate of the world in their hands. Play along on the epic journey filled with danger, mystery, war and love.</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy IX - Disk 4-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.765</rating>
          <releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1550" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy Tactics/Final Fantasy Tactics.cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy Tactics (USA)</name>
          <desc>Lead epic battles in a new Final Fantasy world.&#xA;&#xA;Betrayal and darker dealings await in Square Soft&#39;s game of war.&#xA;&#xA;Fight hundreds of battles across dangerous 3D terrain as an ancient blood feud awakens a deadlier foe.&#xA;&#xA;* Command knights, mages, ninjas and more&#xA;* Based on Final Fantasy characters and magic&#xA;* 19 character classes, 400 abilities&#xA;* Deep customization options&#xA;* In-game interactive manual&#xA;* Only on PlayStation.</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy Tactics-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5875</rating>
          <releasedate>19980128T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Square</developer>
          <publisher>Square</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="525" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy VII/Final Fantasy VII (U) (Disc 2) [SCUS-94164].cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy VII (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>Set in a dystopian world, Final Fantasy VII&#39;s story centers on mercenary Cloud Strife who joins with several others to stop the megacorporation Shinra, which is draining the life of the planet to use as an energy source. As the story progresses, the situation escalates and Cloud and his allies face Sephiroth, the game&#39;s main antagonist.</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy VII (U) (Disc 2) [SCUS-94164]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7697</rating>
          <releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Square</developer>
          <publisher>Square</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="531" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Galerians/Galerians (USA) (Disc 1).cue</path>
          <name>Galerians (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
          <desc>A fleeting memory. A haunting vision. A childhood mystery that can prevent the destruction of mankind. Crave Entertainment, Inc. introduces Galerians, a survival-horror title for the PlayStation that thrusts players into a twisted future.&#xA;&#xA;Rion is a young boy who awakens in a laboratory, unable to remember anything except his name. He soon discovers that he possesses psychic powers, although they come with severe consequences. With only a girl named Lilia, whose voice guides him, Rion must escape his captors and begin putting together the broken shards of his memories.&#xA;&#xA;Players assume the role of Rion and must guide him through four locations in his search for Lilia and the secret of his past. Armed with powerful psychic abilities, Rion must combat human enemies and a variety of frightening genetic experiments. Unfortunately, nothing can prepare him for the confrontation with his own history.&#xA;&#xA;The game spans three discs, combining action and puzzle solving in a horrific setting. Galerians utilizes a third-person perspective and features polygonal characters on pre-rendered backgrounds. The shocking truth is gradually revealed through fragmented visions and confessions, building to an epic struggle between man and machine.</desc>
          <image>./images/Galerians (USA) (Disc 1)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20000329T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Polygon Magic</developer>
          <publisher>Crave</publisher>
          <genre></genre>
      </game>
      <game id="531" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Galerians/Galerians (USA) (Disc 2).cue</path>
          <name>Galerians (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>A fleeting memory. A haunting vision. A childhood mystery that can prevent the destruction of mankind. Crave Entertainment, Inc. introduces Galerians, a survival-horror title for the PlayStation that thrusts players into a twisted future.&#xA;&#xA;Rion is a young boy who awakens in a laboratory, unable to remember anything except his name. He soon discovers that he possesses psychic powers, although they come with severe consequences. With only a girl named Lilia, whose voice guides him, Rion must escape his captors and begin putting together the broken shards of his memories.&#xA;&#xA;Players assume the role of Rion and must guide him through four locations in his search for Lilia and the secret of his past. Armed with powerful psychic abilities, Rion must combat human enemies and a variety of frightening genetic experiments. Unfortunately, nothing can prepare him for the confrontation with his own history.&#xA;&#xA;The game spans three discs, combining action and puzzle solving in a horrific setting. Galerians utilizes a third-person perspective and features polygonal characters on pre-rendered backgrounds. The shocking truth is gradually revealed through fragmented visions and confessions, building to an epic struggle between man and machine.</desc>
          <image>./images/Galerians (USA) (Disc 2)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20000329T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Polygon Magic</developer>
          <publisher>Crave</publisher>
          <genre></genre>
      </game>
      <game id="531" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Galerians/Galerians (USA) (Disc 3).cue</path>
          <name>Galerians (USA) (Disc 3)</name>
          <desc>A fleeting memory. A haunting vision. A childhood mystery that can prevent the destruction of mankind. Crave Entertainment, Inc. introduces Galerians, a survival-horror title for the PlayStation that thrusts players into a twisted future.&#xA;&#xA;Rion is a young boy who awakens in a laboratory, unable to remember anything except his name. He soon discovers that he possesses psychic powers, although they come with severe consequences. With only a girl named Lilia, whose voice guides him, Rion must escape his captors and begin putting together the broken shards of his memories.&#xA;&#xA;Players assume the role of Rion and must guide him through four locations in his search for Lilia and the secret of his past. Armed with powerful psychic abilities, Rion must combat human enemies and a variety of frightening genetic experiments. Unfortunately, nothing can prepare him for the confrontation with his own history.&#xA;&#xA;The game spans three discs, combining action and puzzle solving in a horrific setting. Galerians utilizes a third-person perspective and features polygonal characters on pre-rendered backgrounds. The shocking truth is gradually revealed through fragmented visions and confessions, building to an epic struggle between man and machine.</desc>
          <image>./images/Galerians (USA) (Disc 3)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20000329T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Polygon Magic</developer>
          <publisher>Crave</publisher>
          <genre></genre>
      </game>
      <game id="526" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy VIII/Final Fantasy VIII - Disc 3.cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy VIII (USA) (Disc 3)</name>
          <desc>A member of an elite military team, Squall is forced into a conflict beyond imagination.  To survive, he must contend with a desperate rival, a powerful sorceress, and his own mysterious dreams.&#xA;&#xA;* Realistic, detailed characters and background graphics enhanced by a breathtaking musical score&#xA;* An epic story based on the theme of love, set in a massive new world&#xA;* New Junction System allows characters to be customized with powerful magic spells drawn from enemies&#xA;* Nearly an hour of stunning motion-captured CG cinemas seamlessly integrated into gameplay</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy VIII - Disc 3-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8769199999999999</rating>
          <releasedate>19990211T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Square</developer>
          <publisher>Square</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="13026" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Future Cop L.A.P.D/Future Cop L.A.P.D. [NTSC-U] [SLUS-00739].cue</path>
          <name>Future Cop - L.A.P.D. (USA)</name>
          <desc>The city of Los Angeles has a few more problems than usual in 2100 A.D. You see, the future hasn&#39;t been exactly kind to urban life and now gangs have overrun the already bleak neighborhoods. Is there any hope? There is as long as you enforce the law!&#xA;&#xA;Command a powerful Tactical Assault &amp; Combat X-1 mech walker (that can also transform into a sleek hovercraft) and battle through 12 levels, each culminating in a showdown with a large boss character. Fortunately for you, fourteen different weapons are available to help you teach &#34;crime doesn&#39;t pay.&#34; Feeling a little lonely? If so, a friend can join the action in cooperative play!&#xA;&#xA;An additional game mode, Precinct Assault, has also been included. Precinct Assault is a strategy game that involves two teams (red versus blue) in an all-out battle for supremacy. This mode can be played against the computer or another human. Future Cop: L.A.P.D. supports the Dual Shock Analog Controller to make you feel the gunfire, and progress can be saved using either one block of memory card space or a password.</desc>
          <image>./images/Future Cop L.A.P.D. [NTSC-U] [SLUS-00739]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8</rating>
          <releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>EA Redwood Shores</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="526" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy VIII/Final Fantasy VIII - Disc 4.cue</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy VIII (USA) (Disc 4)</name>
          <desc>A member of an elite military team, Squall is forced into a conflict beyond imagination.  To survive, he must contend with a desperate rival, a powerful sorceress, and his own mysterious dreams.&#xA;&#xA;* Realistic, detailed characters and background graphics enhanced by a breathtaking musical score&#xA;* An epic story based on the theme of love, set in a massive new world&#xA;* New Junction System allows characters to be customized with powerful magic spells drawn from enemies&#xA;* Nearly an hour of stunning motion-captured CG cinemas seamlessly integrated into gameplay</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy VIII - Disc 4-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8769199999999999</rating>
          <releasedate>19990211T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Square</developer>
          <publisher>Square</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="25560" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Gradius Deluxe Pack (J)/Gradius Deluxe Pack (J) SLPS 00303.cue</path>
          <name>Gradius Deluxe Pack (Japan)</name>
          <desc>This pack was released only in Japan and contains both the Arcade classics Gradius I and II.&#xA;It was also ported to Windows 95 and Sega Saturn.</desc>
          <image>./images/Gradius Deluxe Pack (J) SLPS 00303-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19960329T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="13229" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Geki-oh - Shooting King/Geki-oh - Shooting King.cue</path>
          <name>Gekioh - Shooting King (USA)</name>
          <desc>Natsume&#39;s vertical scrolling shooter Gekioh: Shooting King offers nine arcade-style modes of nonstop action in a futuristic setting featuring giant mechs, laser-firing, bomb-dropping airships. Environments are filled with power-ups, explosions, and destructive mayhem. Players wield an arsenal consisting of a devastating Vulcan cannon, electrically charged lightning attacks, and missiles capable of decimating ground tanks and flying squadrons. Power-ups include increases in speed, power, shields, bombs, and point bonuses, with the primary weapon changing depending on the last red (cannon), blue (lightning), or yellow (missile) disk picked up.&#xA;&#xA;Gekioh: Shooting King features three main levels of difficulty: Geki Mode (normal fire rate), Easy Mode (enemies have half the rate of normal fire and collisions aren&#39;t always fatal), and Hard Mode (double firing rate and stacked odds). Six bonus modes are available from the beginning of the game (no unlocking required) and offer diversity in gameplay. Modes include Comical (damage accompanied by a laugh track), Stingy (one aircraft and one special weapon), No Mercy (unerring enemy fire), Slow (slow enemy fire but rate-multiplied), Ancient (bleached out color to eliminate power-up recognition), and Pocket (block-shaped symbols in basic form).</desc>
          <image>./images/Geki-oh - Shooting King-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20021201T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Warashi</developer>
          <publisher>Natsume</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="10249" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Hot Shots Golf 2/Hot Shots Golf 2.cue</path>
          <name>Hot Shots Golf 2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Golf for the people.&#xA;Hot Shots Golf&#39;s award-winning gameplay returns.&#xA;&#xA;-13 golfers who&#39;d probably under-tip the valet&#xA;-7 glorious courses&#xA;-All new Tournament Mode&#xA;-Equipment upgrades for the true fanatic&#xA;-Unrivaled 3D graphics</desc>
          <image>./images/Hot Shots Golf 2-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Clap Hanz</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Sports</genre>
          <players>4</players>
      </game>
      <game id="8510" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Grandia/Grandia - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Grandia (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>Embark On An Unforgettable Journey.&#xA;Travel across vast worlds and unravel the threads of an ancient legend in a quest that challenges your courage. A luminous empire. An ominous secret. An unbelieveable, intriguing adventure.&#xA;&#xA;-Over 200 weapons, enemies and items to collect.&#xA;-More than 80 magic spells and battle techniques.&#xA;-A unique magic and character development system that puts your strategic skills to the test.&#xA;&#xA;Warm and enchanting worlds each with their own architectural style.&#xA;&#xA;Over 80 hours of gameplay. Can you solve the mysteries of Grandia?</desc>
          <image>./images/Grandia - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.65</rating>
          <releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Game Arts</developer>
          <publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="12037" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Jojo&#39;s Bizarre Adventure/Jojo&#39;s Bizarre Adventure.cue</path>
          <name>JoJo&#39;s Bizarre Adventure (USA)</name>
          <desc>JoJo&#39;s Bizarre Adventure has its roots in the realm of the comic book. Players will be able to take control of Jotaro Kujo, his friends, and his enemies in this world hopping, globe spanning fighting fest. Now PlayStation gamers will be able to take a Stand and wallop their friends over the head with them in the comfort of their own home.&#xA;&#xA;This game offers much of the two dimensional fighting fare that Capcom is renowned for. It takes a side venture into new realms with the addition of your Stand partners however. When you whip out a special attack or some hits, a phantasmal apparition will appear to give you back up. Each one differs depending on the characters alignment along the Tarot spectrum, and players also have the ability to put their Stand into a more active role once they build up their Stand Gauge. Then your alter egos can weigh in and have the ability to set up painful chain combos and they enable special character abilities like double jumping and air attacks.</desc>
          <image>./images/Jojo&#39;s Bizarre Adventure-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20001201T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Fighting</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="10962" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Jumping Flash/Jumping Flash.cue</path>
          <name>Jumping Flash! (USA)</name>
          <desc>&#34;...simply superb&#34; Next Generation&#xA;&#xA;The evil Baron Aloha has seized the planet&#39;s six worlds as his own private retreat. Commandeer Robbit, the jumping, shooting robotic rabbit, on a mission to stomp out the royal menace and his gang of pests. Save the planet... if you can keep from losing your lunch!&#xA;&#xA;* A VERY original concept! This adventure takes a giant leap forward as state-of-the-art technology meets action/strategy.&#xA;* The 1st person perspective immerses you into a 3-D fantasy. Hop and soar with realistic views and rapid perspective changes guaranteed to look and feel like the real thing.&#xA;* 18 levels and incredible bonus stages will overwhelm you with vivid graphics.&#xA;* Rapid-fire shots, special weapons and plenty of power-ups!</desc>
          <image>./images/Jumping Flash-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19950428T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Exact</developer>
          <publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="560" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Legend of Mana/Legend of Mana.cue</path>
          <name>Legend of Mana (USA)</name>
          <desc>Create Your World&#xA;In ancient times, the world was saved from destruction by sealing locations and events within magical artifacts. Now, you have the chance to recreate this world as you desire by discovering artifacts, placing them, and exploring the mysteries inside.&#xA;&#xA;-Construct a unique world map and story by carefully placing artifacts.&#xA;-Explore areas in any order, encountering nearly 70 different gameplay scenarios.&#xA;-Battle enemies in real-time with special attacks and customizable controls.&#xA;-Control every aspect of your new world: raise faithful net monsters, create powerful golems, forge mighty weapons, and refine magical instruments.&#xA;-Adventure with a friend by having them import their Legend of Mana character from a MEMORY CARD, or take control of an NPC .</desc>
          <image>./images/Legend of Mana-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.85</rating>
          <releasedate>20000607T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="10826" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Medal of Honor/Medal of Honor.cue</path>
          <name>Medal of Honor (USA)</name>
          <desc>Medal of Honor is the first in the long-running series of World War II shooters, originally created by Steven Spielberg. The play assumes the role of Lt. Patterson who has to complete different tasks in the OSS. The missions vary from securing a small French village from any Nazi forces, to taking out a Heavy armored German rail gun. The player has access to a wide selection of antique weapons such as P38 pistols, M1 Garand carabines, MP40&#39;s and more. The goals also include undercover missions. Split-screen multiplayer is supported for two players.</desc>
          <image>./images/Medal of Honor-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.85</rating>
          <releasedate>19991111T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Dreamworks</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="17378" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mr. Driller/Mr. Driller [U] [SLUS-01111].cue</path>
          <name>Mr. Driller (USA)</name>
          <desc>Mr Driller is a real-time puzzle game that relies solely on quick-thinking and a bit of planning. Gameplay is a combination of Tetris and Boulder Dash: You have to drill down through multi-colored blocks to reach the bottom while avoiding the consequences of reckless drilling (blocks may fall on you and crush you).</desc>
          <image>./images/Mr. Driller [U] [SLUS-01111]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20000701T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Namco</developer>
          <publisher>Namco</publisher>
          <genre>Puzzle</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="21322" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Monster Rancher 2/Monster Rancher 2.cue</path>
          <name>Monster Rancher 2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Monster Rancher 2 is at heart an arena fighting game with a lot of ancillary game play thrown in. As a trainer of a fighting monster you have to train, reward, punish, cajole and bribe your minion to build up its statistics. You then take your monster into the arena where it battles with other monsters for cash prizes, prestige, and better stats. Like the original Monster Rancher, this game allows players to create a monster using an innovative technique: you can stick in any CD you own (PlayStation, audio, PC, or other) and the data that is read off the CD is used to generate the characteristics of the monster.</desc>
          <image>./images/Monster Rancher 2-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19990225T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tecmo</developer>
          <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="8774" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mega Man X6/Mega Man X6.cue</path>
          <name>Mega Man X6 (USA) (v1.0)</name>
          <desc>Mission Critical... Zero is Missing... Search and Rescue!&#xA;&#xA;It&#39;s been three weeks since Earth&#39;s near collision with the space colony Eurasia. The disaster was averted by Zero&#39;s heroics. Now, on a bruised and battered planet, tales of rampaging reploids are surfacing. It&#39;s up to Mega Man X to investigate these mysteries but it&#39;s not going to be easy. Mega Man X must battle through a maze of levels and rescue reploids along the way. Return to battle again and again with the new Nightmare System, which randomizes level maps, enemies, and endings based on how you play the game. Mega Man X is back and now it&#39;s personal!&#xA;&#xA;* The next action packed-adventure in the Mega Man X legacy – help find Zero!&#xA;* Collect stronger powerups by rescuing as many reploids as you can&#xA;* Mega Man X now access Zero&#39;s sword as a new weapon&#xA;* New Nightmare System – randomizes level maps, enemies and endings based on how you play the game</desc>
          <image>./images/Mega Man X6-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>20011204T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="13763" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Need for Speed, The/Need for Speed, The.cue</path>
          <name>Road &amp; Track Presents - The Need for Speed (USA)</name>
          <desc>Drive some of your favourite sports cars through wild and fast tracks, including the Dodge Viper, Lamborghini, Ferrari, Porshe, Corvette, Mazda RX7, Toyota Supra Turbo, and Acura NSX. Some of the tracks are open road, meaning you simply fly down a huge highway, with cops following in hot pursuit. One of the options in the game allows you to pick which time of the day to race in.</desc>
          <image>./images/Need for Speed, The-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19970527T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Pioneer Productions</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="588" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Omega Boost/Omega Boost.cue</path>
          <name>Omega Boost (USA)</name>
          <desc>Co-Existence between man and machine is no longer an option. The fate of humankind is hanging by a fiber... time is running out.&#xA;&#xA;-Pilot Omega Boost in a high-intensity action shooter across 19 diverse zones.&#xA;-Multiple mission objectives, lethal ground and air assaults and deadly cyber-drogues.&#xA;-Free-float in dizzying 360o combat.&#xA;-Scan for targets, fire Vulcan guns and bag those bogeys with laser lock-on in the ultimate space dogfights!&#xA;-Customize and upgrade equipment and weaponry with every win.&#xA;-Review intense battles with the Replay Mode.</desc>
          <image>./images/Omega Boost-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19990422T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="2420" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Oddworld - Abe&#39;s Oddysey/Oddworld - Abe&#39;s Oddysee [NTSC-U] [SLUS-00190].cue</path>
          <name>Oddworld - Abe&#39;s Oddysee (USA) (v1.0)</name>
          <desc>In a lush of diabolical danger where everyone wants to eat you, you&#39;re the skinny guy with no weapons. Run, jump, hide, scramble and talk your way past the ugliest bunch of carnivorous crustaceans ever created. Unlock Abe&#39;s special powers then figure out your foes, and you might save your race. Don&#39;t, and you&#39;re dinner! Enter Oddworld&#39;s surreal, sensory overload of pure gaming and claim your destiny.</desc>
          <image>./images/Oddworld - Abe&#39;s Oddysee [NTSC-U] [SLUS-00190]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.68182</rating>
          <releasedate>19970901T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Oddworld Inhabitants</developer>
          <publisher>GT Interactive Software</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="25027" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Parodius IV (J)/Parodius IV (J).cue</path>
          <name>Jikkyou Oshaberi Parodius - Forever with Me (Japan)</name>
          <desc>This game is the fourth game in the series of parody shooters produced by Konami and was released only in Japan. The gameplay is stylistically very similar to the Gradius series, but the graphics and music are intentionally absurd. The game, as its name would suggest (translated: &#34;Chatting Parodius Live&#34;), contains a large amount of Japanese voice samples shouted out in a style similar to that of a game show host.&#xA;&#xA;Unlike the previous titles, this game was not created originally as an Arcade game. Instead, it was originally released on the japanese Super Famicom and this port is an upgraded version of that one, featuring not only improved graphics and sound from the Super Famicom game, but some altered levels and bosses, including a cheat to replace &#34;Tokimeki People&#39;s Dance&#34; with an enhanced version, &#34;Days Of The Dream&#39;s Memories&#34;. Also added were several &#34;Omake&#34; stages and an unlockable Dracula-kun and Kid Dracula as a playable character. In a two-player game, both players can now choose to play simultaneously instead of just alternately in the Super Famicom game.&#xA;&#xA;This game was also released on the Sega Saturn with little differences compared to this version.</desc>
          <image>./images/Parodius IV (J)-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19961220T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Stone Heads</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="592" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Persona 2 - Eternal Punishment/Persona 2 - Bonus Disk.cue</path>
          <name>Persona 2 - Eternal Punishment (USA) (Bonus Disc)</name>
          <desc>Welcome back to the twisted world of Persona, where nightmares become reality and reality becomes a nightmare... Over 50 hours of dark twisted gameplay, plus stunning anime cinematics that absorb you into the intriguing world of Persona! Enlist the help of the nightmarish denizens of Persona through the use of the unique &#34;Contact System!&#34; Unleash total devastation by combining over 80 Persona to defeat the minions of evil. Change the fate of your characters by employing the revolutionary &#34;Rumor System.&#34;</desc>
          <image>./images/Persona 2 - Bonus Disk-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.8</rating>
          <releasedate>20001222T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Atlus</developer>
          <publisher>Atlus</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="25829" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Puyo Puyo Sun (J)/Puyo Puyo Sun - Ketteiban (Japan) (v1.0).cue</path>
          <name>Puyo Puyo Sun - Ketteiban (Japan) (v1.0)</name>
          <desc>This game is a Japan-only port of the third game in the Puyo Puyo series originally made for the Arcades by Sega.&#xA;&#xA;The name of Puyo Puyo Sun comes from a Japanese pun on &#34;san&#34;, and also indicates a new Ojama brought into the game. As Sun Puyos were used in this game, and the game itself is not only set on a tropical beach, but is the third in the series (三, &#34;san&#34; is the Japanese word for the number 3), the name suited the game. &#xA;&#xA;Just like the predecessors, Puyos fall from the top of the screen in pairs, can be moved left and right, and can be rotated clockwise and anti-clockwise by 90°. The rule of Sousai and Zenkesei still remained, but every time you countered, special garbage would fall on the screen in a preset pattern (in the Game Boy version of this game, it fell randomly). Every time you cleared the screen however, Sun Puyos would fall on the screen, and the All Clear bonus removed.&#xA;&#xA;The game features 3 story modes featuring their own character and difficulty: Draco Centauros (Easy), Arle Nadja (Normal) and Schezo Wegey (Hard).&#xA;&#xA;Storyline: &#xA;Satan has once again decided to create another test by using special magic to pull the Sun closer to the Earth on a remote island. This created a semi-resort, in which characters have decided to visit. Arle, together with Carbuncle, find the sun too hot, and see the building that Satan&#39;s emanating his own heat wave. Draco loves the hot weather and appears in a bikini, whereas Schezo, who takes refuge in a cave, finds that it&#39;s just not cool enough, and decides to find out what&#39;s happening.</desc>
          <image>./images/Puyo Puyo Sun - Ketteiban (Japan) (v1.0)-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19971127T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Compile</developer>
          <publisher>Compile</publisher>
          <genre>Puzzle</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="9332" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Parasite Eve 2/Parasite Eve 2 - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Parasite Eve II (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
          <desc>Aya Brea is back. The Neo Mitochondrion Creature infestation has resurfaced and taken on a sinister twist. The outcome of this battle will determine earth&#39;s dominant species. Horrifying CG cinemas and sharper graphics bring the shocking new storyline to life as Aya hunts for the source of the outbreak. Fully-upgradable weapons, customizable armor, and a new, real-time battle system will aid in the conflict, along with powerful new Parasite Energy abilities.</desc>
          <image>./images/Parasite Eve 2 - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.62</rating>
          <releasedate>20000112T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Horror</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11730" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Point Blank 3/Point Blank 3 [SLUS-01354].cue</path>
          <name>Point Blank 3 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The escapades of Namco&#39;s Dr. Dan and Dr. Don continue in Point Blank 3, the third edition of the irreverent, mini-game based light-gun series. A selection of 80 events are offered, many of which thrust the hapless duo into situations that require timely intervention by the player on their behalf, testing your reflexes and shooting accuracy at the same time. The myriad of events present the player with basic tasks that range in both scope and difficulty. A plethora of mini-game formats are provided that include shooting color-coded targets to protecting the two numbskulls from threatening objects, to those that require the player to perform rudimentary mathematics calculations before shooting the correct answer. Cameo appearances by Tekken characters, classic Namco franchises and other such in-jokes abound in the many scenarios players will find themselves embroiled.</desc>
          <image>./images/Point Blank 3 [SLUS-01354]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20010516T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tose Software</developer>
          <publisher>Namco</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="21323" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Parodius V (J)/Parodius V (J).cue</path>
          <name>Sexy Parodius (Japan)</name>
          <desc>Sexy Parodius (セクシーパロディウス Sekushī Parodiusu?) is a scrolling shooter arcade game. It is the fifth installment of the Parodius series, produced by Konami. Like the rest of the series, it is a parody of the Gradius series and other Konami games. It also contains explicitly sexual level and enemy designs and risqué innuendo. Many level bosses are women in various erotic costumes (such as the &#34;bunny costume&#34; modeled on Playboy Bunnies) or various states of undress.&#xA;&#xA;While this game was never released officially in the West, Konami released for Arcades in 1996 an alternate rarer Asian version that was fully localized in English.</desc>
          <image>./images/Parodius V (J)-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="599" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./R4/R4.cue</path>
          <name>R4 - Ridge Racer Type 4 (USA)</name>
          <desc>&#34;R4 has to be the best-looking PlayStation racer ever (yes, edging out even Gran Turismo).&#34; – Official PlayStation Magazine, December 1998&#xA;&#xA;* 8 tracks, 45 unique car models, and over 300 different car variations.&#xA;* Sensational graphics and lighting effects give every race a cinematic feel.&#xA;* Battle head-to-head in the 2-player, split screen VS mode.&#xA;* Experience all the ups and downs of a full racing season with your team in the Grand Prix Mode.&#xA;* New cars awarded based on your performance in every race.&#xA;* Design original logos to customize your car.</desc>
          <image>./images/R4-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19990504T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Namco</developer>
          <publisher>Namco</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11788" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./RayStorm/RayStorm [SLUS-00482].cue</path>
          <name>RayStorm (USA)</name>
          <desc>The year is 2219 and the Secilia Federation has initiated a plan to destroy Earth. So far, the evil federation has been highly successful in destroying much of the planet&#39;s defensive forces and resources. With world destruction at hand, the fate of mankind is looking for a savior.&#xA;&#xA;Unbeknownst to the federation, the Star Federation, an Earth-based organization, has been developing two highly sophisticated aircraft known as the R-Gray prototypes. These destructive machines are packed with homing missiles, laser cannons and other crippling weapons. As the planet&#39;s hero, you&#39;ll control either R-Gray ship, taking to the skies in a desperate mission to stop the Secilia Federation from carrying out their plans.</desc>
          <image>./images/RayStorm [SLUS-00482]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Taito</developer>
          <publisher>Spaz (Working Designs)</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11796" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Ridge Racer/Ridge Racer.cue</path>
          <name>Ridge Racer (USA)</name>
          <desc>You want to drive fast? Really fast? Nothing provides the adrenaline-charged rush of speed like Ridge Racer. State-of-the-art features, amazing control, neck-snapping acceleration and true-to-road realism make this the only racing game you&#39;ll ever need. Ever. And please, always wear a helmet.</desc>
          <image>./images/Ridge Racer-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19950909T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Namco</developer>
          <publisher>Namco</publisher>
          <genre>Racing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="568" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Rockman - Battle &amp; Chase (J)/Rockman - Battle &amp; Chase (Japan) (v1.1).cue</path>
          <name>Rockman - Battle &amp; Chase (Japan) (v1.1)</name>
          <desc>It&#39;s robot mayhem at the Battle &amp; Chase tournament! Dr. Wily is trying to take over the tournament with his army of Robot Masters, and now Mega Man has to enter to try and save the races! Choose your racer and head out on the tracks, and if you win, you&#39;ll get to steal parts off your opponent&#39;s cars, and eventually, you&#39;ll race against the mad Dr. Wily himself!</desc>
          <image>./images/Rockman - Battle &amp; Chase (Japan) (v1.1)-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19981130T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11804" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Road Rash/Road Rash [U] [SLUS-00035].cue</path>
          <name>Road Rash (USA)</name>
          <desc>Electronic Arts&#39; motorcycle racing series makes its PlayStation debut with digitized graphics, a licensed soundtrack, and full-motion video cut-scenes. The fourth entry in the franchise continues the point-to-point racing format of the Genesis games, with players knocking out rivals with fists, boots, or even pilfered weapons. Two play options are available to rambunctious riders: Thrash Mode and Big Game Mode. The former lets players enter a single race on their choice of courses and difficulty levels, while the latter is structured like a career. Big Game Mode involves selecting one of eight colorful characters and competing in a total of 25 races on five Californian courses: Sierra Nevada, Napa Valley, Peninsula, The City, and Pacific Highway.</desc>
          <image>./images/Road Rash [U] [SLUS-00035]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19951229T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
          <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="12396" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Saiyuki - Journey West/Saiyuki - Journey West.cue</path>
          <name>Saiyuki - Journey West (USA)</name>
          <desc>A Journey of Friendship...A Journey fraught with Danger...A Journey to Save the World...A Journey West. Based on one of the most popular legends of China, Saiyuki takes you on an epic journey from China to India and back. Recruit the Monkey King, Son Goku, and others like them to defeat untold monsters along the way.</desc>
          <image>./images/Saiyuki - Journey West-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>20010813T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>KOEI</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="25843" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Salamander - Deluxe Pack Plus (J)/Salamander - Deluxe Pack Plus (JPN).cue</path>
          <name>Salamander Deluxe Pack Plus (Japan)</name>
          <desc>Contains the three Konami Arcade Classics:&#xA;&#xA;- Salamander&#xA;- Salamander 2&#xA;- Life Force</desc>
          <image>./images/Salamander - Deluxe Pack Plus (JPN)-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19970703T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11438" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Strider/Strider [NTSC-U] [SLUS-01142].cue</path>
          <name>Strider (USA)</name>
          <desc>A PlayStation version of Strider was produced by Capcom, which was first released in 2000 as a second disc which came packaged with the PlayStation version of Strider 2. The North American release has the Strider and Strider 2 game code pressed onto the wrong disc (so to play Strider you actually need to insert the Strider 2 disc).</desc>
          <image>./images/Strider [NTSC-U] [SLUS-01142]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="13577" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Star Ocean 2/Star Ocean 2 - Disk 1.cue</path>
          <name>Star Ocean - The Second Story (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
          <desc>The game gives the player the choice of playing as Rena or Claude, with the journey evolving and ending differently depending on the choices one makes.&#xA;&#xA;Star Ocean: The Second Story is a world of magic, science, space travel and deadly demons! Enter a world where love knows no bounds, the evil is neverending and good can overcome all if the heart is just and true. Featuring three battle modes, the ability to master skills to create items and an emotional level for each of the characters, Enix has pulled out all the stops in their latest (and first) title to be brought to the North American PlayStation.&#xA;&#xA;Star Ocean: The Second Story takes place twenty years after the original game, Star Ocean. Roughly the first half of the plot of the game takes place on the planet Expel, an underdeveloped planet on the verge of its industrial age. On Expel kings still rule over great kingdoms, swords and sorcery dominate the battlefield, and sailing ships are still made from wood. According to a Federation law, named the Undeveloped Planet Protection Treaty, a planet with such a level of civilization may not be directly contacted under any but the most dire circumstances—and even then, contact must be minimal and secretive. This law is reminiscent of Star Trek&#39;s Prime Directive.</desc>
          <image>./images/Star Ocean 2 - Disk 1-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.9</rating>
          <releasedate>19990531T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tri-ace</developer>
          <publisher>Enix</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="13577" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Star Ocean 2/Star Ocean 2 - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Star Ocean - The Second Story (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>The game gives the player the choice of playing as Rena or Claude, with the journey evolving and ending differently depending on the choices one makes.&#xA;&#xA;Star Ocean: The Second Story is a world of magic, science, space travel and deadly demons! Enter a world where love knows no bounds, the evil is neverending and good can overcome all if the heart is just and true. Featuring three battle modes, the ability to master skills to create items and an emotional level for each of the characters, Enix has pulled out all the stops in their latest (and first) title to be brought to the North American PlayStation.&#xA;&#xA;Star Ocean: The Second Story takes place twenty years after the original game, Star Ocean. Roughly the first half of the plot of the game takes place on the planet Expel, an underdeveloped planet on the verge of its industrial age. On Expel kings still rule over great kingdoms, swords and sorcery dominate the battlefield, and sailing ships are still made from wood. According to a Federation law, named the Undeveloped Planet Protection Treaty, a planet with such a level of civilization may not be directly contacted under any but the most dire circumstances—and even then, contact must be minimal and secretive. This law is reminiscent of Star Trek&#39;s Prime Directive.</desc>
          <image>./images/Star Ocean 2 - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.9</rating>
          <releasedate>19990531T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tri-ace</developer>
          <publisher>Enix</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11439" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Strider 2/Strider 2.cue</path>
          <name>Strider 2 (USA)</name>
          <desc>Strider 2 is a fast-paced, arcade-style action game. Unlike its predecessor, it features 2D animations placed on 3D backgrounds. There is a range of new moves including a double jump, backward somersault and dash, which allows him to perform longer jumps. He also has the ability to boost his weapon, the Cypher sword, enabling it to release homing plasma waves. There is also a Savage Slash attack, with random slashes.&#xA;&#xA;There are numerous bonuses that can be collected in the levels. These either boost Strider&#39;s vitality, increase the power of his sword or increase the player&#39;s game score. Another addition to the game is a Boss Gauge which lets the player know how much energy the mid- or end of level boss has left before it dies.</desc>
          <image>./images/Strider 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>20000729T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11675" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Threads of Fate/Threads of Fate.cue</path>
          <name>Threads of Fate (USA)</name>
          <desc>Two Amazing Adventures!&#xA;&#xA;Rue is on a quest to revive a lost friend. Mint is seeking power and revenge. Both of them are looking for a powerful relic, but which will be brave and clever enough to reach their goal?&#xA;Explore a beautifully rendered 3D world filled with challenging puzzles, unusual enemies, and unknown dangers&#xA;Play as both characters to encounter two entirely different storylines&#xA;Rue has the ability to shape-shift into the forms of defeated enemies&#xA;Mint can learn and use a wide variety of powerful magic spells</desc>
          <image>./images/Threads of Fate-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20000718T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="8558" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Vandal Hearts II/Vandal Hearts II.cue</path>
          <name>Vandal Hearts II (USA)</name>
          <desc>Vandal Hearts II is a turn based strategic RPG which is comparable to the more famous Fire Emblem series.&#xA;&#xA;Most of the gameplay consists of moving your party on 3D grid based maps in a way that will give you a strategic advantage over your enemies. The main difference between Vandal Hearts II and its predecessor is the change of the battle system. Unlike in Vandal Hearts you and your enemies issue the commands at the same time and then move simultaneously. That results in in completely new strategies and gives the game a unique touch.&#xA;&#xA;The story takes place in the already collapsed church state of Nirvadia, that was once formed by the religious leader St Nirvath, but eventually ceased to exist, because of several conflicts between unbelievers and local rulers. Caused by a chain of coincidences, the young boy Joshua, from a small and unimportant village in the east, eventually finds himself within a complex political scheme set in motion by power-hungry aristocrats and religious fanatics.</desc>
          <image>./images/Vandal Hearts II-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6333300000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="2292" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Um Jammer Lammy/Um Jammer Lammy [NTSC-U] [SCUS-94448].cue</path>
          <name>Um Jammer Lammy (USA)</name>
          <desc>There is a new rock star in town. Where Lammy goes mosh pits follow. She&#39;s the guitar-slinging megastar of an all-chick band called Milkcan. Help Lammy make it to her big gig on time by jamming to rock, heavy metal, punk, pop and other killer riffs.&#xA;You can even take on another player to an awesome two-player mode.&#xA;Um Jammer Lammy, yeah...it rocks</desc>
          <image>./images/Um Jammer Lammy [NTSC-U] [SCUS-94448]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19990731T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>NanaOn-Sha</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Music</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="3667" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Vagrant Story/Vagrant Story.cue</path>
          <name>Vagrant Story (USA)</name>
          <desc>Vagrant Story is a role-playing game with several distinguishing characteristics. The entire game (including the numerous cutscenes that advance the plot) is rendered in 3D. The game focuses on exploration of large, complex dungeon-like areas and combat; there are no &#34;friendly&#34; areas, NPC interaction, or monetary system. Dungeons contain many optional rooms and environmental puzzles that mostly involve pushing, destroying, and re-arranging different types of crates to access higher areas. Ashley can also jump and grab ledges of higher platforms during exploration.</desc>
          <image>./images/Vagrant Story-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6599999999999999</rating>
          <releasedate>20000515T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Squaresoft</developer>
          <publisher>Square EA</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11640" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Wild Arms 2/Wild Arms 2 - Disk 1.cue</path>
          <name>Wild Arms 2 (USA) (Disc 1)</name>
          <desc>Wild Arms 2 is not a direct sequel to the first Wild Arms, although it is set in the same fictional world Filgaia, which combines elements of Old West, steampunk, and fantasy. The turn-based combat system against randomly appearing enemies resembles that of the predecessor, featuring techniques unique to each character, as well as the Guardian system, which allows the characters to summon powerful creatures to assist them in battles. Three combatants can be used actively in battles; the player can also switch any of them with a reserve character, up to six altogether.</desc>
          <image>./images/Wild Arms 2 - Disk 1-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20000430T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Media Vision</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="23753" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Zanac X Zanac (J)/Zanac X Zanac (J) [SLPS-03354].cue</path>
          <name>Zanac X Zanac (Japan)</name>
          <desc>The Celebration of a Classic Compile&#39;d in a New Way.&#xA;&#xA;In 2001 veteran &#34;shmup&#34; and puzzle game developer Compile, released Zanac X Zanac to the Japanesse market for play on the Sony Playstation. It came out on the 15th anniversary of the original Zanac.&#xA;&#xA;Zanac X Zanac consists of two separate games; the original Zanac(in various iterations) and the debut of Zanac Neo. It can best be described as part classic compilation, part updated re-imagining of the original.&#xA;&#xA;Zanac&#xA;Zanac is a top down, 2D, vertical scrolling, space shooter. Gameplay consists of frantic scrambles between dodging bullets, shooting down enemies, and powering-up your spacecraft. The original Zanac game released in Japan in 1986 for the MSX home computer and the Family Computer Disk System(Famicom Disk System). Zanac proved to be one of Compile&#39;s more popular titles thanks to it&#39;s eventual US release on the Nintendo Entertainment System that same year.&#xA;&#xA;There are two things that may stand-out to Zanac players; it&#39;s frantic pace, and it&#39;s ever-changing playfield. Rarely are two games of Zanac identical. This is due to the games innovative use of the company coined &#34;A.I.&#34; system. The game was programmed in a manner that gives a slightly different experience with each play. Things such as enemy type, enemy speed, and enemy placement are adjusted in real-time based on the players skill level, number of lives, and power-up configuration(similar to &#34;rank&#34; systems found in shooters such as Battle Garegga many years later). Many shooters at the time relied on pattern memorization. Zanac demands a player to be ever mindful of the dynamic play-field.&#xA;&#xA;Weapon Power-Ups&#xA;&#xA;At the start of a game, or a new life, the player may feel terribly under-powered. However, Zanac has a robust power-up system that allows your spacecraft to become very powerful. A rapid and constant cycle between the player feeling under-powered one second then awesomely overpowered the next is typical throughout a game of Zanac. The player starts with a standard rapid-fire shot(pea shooter), and a &#34;0&#34; level sub-weapon.&#xA;&#xA;The sub-weapon can be changed or upgraded several times depending on the players tastes/gameplay situation. This is done through collecting floating power-ups during gameplay which are numbered ranging from &#34;0&#34; to &#34;7&#34;. Each number represents a different type of sub-weapon with a unique form of attack. By collecting different numbers, the player will switch sub-weapons. By collecting the same number the players current sub-weapon is upgraded to become more powerful, up to 3 times.&#xA;&#xA;The players standard rapid-fire shot can also be upgraded by collecting a different type of power-up in the form of yellow &#34;orbs&#34;. The orbs are only found within blue blocks that scroll down from the top of the screen. The blocks must be shot apart to reveal the possible orb within. Some blocks do not house orbs, and instead treat the player to a scatter-shot of deadly bullets. Other than powering-up the standard rapid-fire shot, another key component of the orbs are that when they&#39;re collected they provide momentary invulnerability. This is a key strategic maneuver if you plan to last through the difficult levels of Zanac.&#xA;&#xA;Included versions of Zanac&#xA;&#xA;Zanac X Zanac contains two classic iterations of the the original Zanac as well as two exclusive modes:&#xA;&#xA;- &#34;Disk Version&#34;(Family Computer Disk System version)&#xA;&#xA;- &#34;Rom Version&#34;(Nintendo Entertainment System version)&#xA;&#xA;- &#34;Special Version&#34;(enhanced graphics/sound, exclusive mode)&#xA;&#xA;- &#34;Score Trial&#34;(single level score attack, exclusive mode, also in Neo)&#xA;&#xA;Each version includes a &#34;save&#34; and &#34;load&#34; feature. This allows for recoding of high-scores and the ability to continue from the level previously reached. Continues are unlimited however, your score will reset upon &#34;Game Over&#34;. These features are also included in Zanac Neo.&#xA;&#xA;Zanac Neo&#xA;Zanac Neo is a top down, 2D, vertically scrolling space shooter. The game shares nearly the same gameplay as the original Zanac. The signature &#34;0&#34; - &#34;7&#34; numbered power-up system makes a return, as well as the yellow orbs that augment your standard shot and provide momentary invulnerability. The graphics, music, and sound effects have all been updated. More detailed and interesting backgrounds were added to the levels, and music from the original game returns in remix form.&#xA;&#xA;One of the major additions to &#34;Neo&#34; is being able to select from 3 different ships upon starting the game. Each ship has slightly different movement/shooting properties and each have slightly different sub-weapon implementation. In the spirit of the original game, there are still 8 different sub-weapons that can be picked-up and upgraded during play, allowing for a variety of unique weapon combinations for each ship.&#xA;&#xA;Another addition comes in the form of a new type of &#34;power-shot&#34;. As enemies are destroyed a bar fills at the bottom of the screen allowing for the player to unleash a powerful beam shot. When the bar is completely filled a bomb can also be fired that can clear enemies and/or set-off a chain reaction of orb-block explosions.&#xA;&#xA;Zanac Neo supports two player simultaneous play, a first in Zanac history.</desc>
          <image>./images/Zanac X Zanac (J) [SLPS-03354]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20011129T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Compile</developer>
          <publisher>Compile</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="11640" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Wild Arms 2/Wild Arms 2 - Disk 2.cue</path>
          <name>Wild Arms 2 (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>Wild Arms 2 is not a direct sequel to the first Wild Arms, although it is set in the same fictional world Filgaia, which combines elements of Old West, steampunk, and fantasy. The turn-based combat system against randomly appearing enemies resembles that of the predecessor, featuring techniques unique to each character, as well as the Guardian system, which allows the characters to summon powerful creatures to assist them in battles. Three combatants can be used actively in battles; the player can also switch any of them with a reserve character, up to six altogether.</desc>
          <image>./images/Wild Arms 2 - Disk 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>20000430T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Media Vision</developer>
          <publisher>Sony</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="11730" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Point Blank 3/Point Blank 3 [SLUS-01354].bin</path>
          <name>Point Blank 3 (USA)</name>
          <desc>The escapades of Namco&#39;s Dr. Dan and Dr. Don continue in Point Blank 3, the third edition of the irreverent, mini-game based light-gun series. A selection of 80 events are offered, many of which thrust the hapless duo into situations that require timely intervention by the player on their behalf, testing your reflexes and shooting accuracy at the same time. The myriad of events present the player with basic tasks that range in both scope and difficulty. A plethora of mini-game formats are provided that include shooting color-coded targets to protecting the two numbskulls from threatening objects, to those that require the player to perform rudimentary mathematics calculations before shooting the correct answer. Cameo appearances by Tekken characters, classic Namco franchises and other such in-jokes abound in the many scenarios players will find themselves embroiled.</desc>
          <image>./images/Point Blank 3 [SLUS-01354]-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>20010516T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tose Software</developer>
          <publisher>Namco</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="11574" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Command &amp; Conquer/Command &amp; Conquer [NOD Disc] [SLUS-00410].bin</path>
          <name>Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 2) (NOD)</name>
          <desc>Command &amp; Conquer develops ideas from Westwood&#39;s previous game Dune 2, forming a real-time strategy (RTS) game. The control system involves selecting units with the mouse and then directing them, while the opponents make their moves without waiting for a &#34;turn&#34; to end.&#xA;&#xA;The game focuses on a war between two organizations, The Brotherhood of Nod and the Global Defense Initiative. The player can take control of either side for more than 15 missions. Both have different units and structures, including artillery, tanks and light infantry.</desc>
          <image>./images/Command &amp; Conquer [NOD Disc] [SLUS-00410]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Westwood</developer>
          <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
          <genre>Strategy</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="525" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Final Fantasy VII/Final Fantasy VII (U) (Disc 2) [SCUS-94164].bin</path>
          <name>Final Fantasy VII (USA) (Disc 2)</name>
          <desc>Set in a dystopian world, Final Fantasy VII&#39;s story centers on mercenary Cloud Strife who joins with several others to stop the megacorporation Shinra, which is draining the life of the planet to use as an energy source. As the story progresses, the situation escalates and Cloud and his allies face Sephiroth, the game&#39;s main antagonist.</desc>
          <image>./images/Final Fantasy VII (U) (Disc 2) [SCUS-94164]-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7697</rating>
          <releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Square</developer>
          <publisher>Square</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
  </gameList>